嗯
hello
大家晚上好晚上好
我是来自古力高萨特里说的普通社员
明天狼一三
晚上好
感谢大家在开播之前进行的投票投票统计
下来
一票之差
双数得到了得到了胜利啊
我们今天先来探究这个悬案
好吧
上一票之差先有人投的一吗
然后连续三个人投的二
然后再有一个人投一
然后再有一个人直接文字
文字点出了双数预知答案了
你也你也算做投票的呀
那这种也算做投票的
还是盲选
就给盲选吧
其实这两个是在同一个捆绑包里面的
之前买的小的是今天玩其中一个刚刚好
一个单数
一个双数来着
就只不过单数的话
它是刚刚好
可能今天晚上一个流程就能玩完的
还有明票和暗票
嗯
是的
这两个很细很肉
而且直接一个捆绑包就可以拿了吗
好像悬安吃个玩的更多一点
桌面探索者可能表面上看起来要更接近之
前那个像鲁
特黎加六六六那种吧
悬案的话内容看起来可能会更好
谢巫破谢巫魄的人气票内容看起来可能更
多一些
还有六十多嗯
还有一个催泪姐妹
叫人鱼面具哦
这个没有看到
主要是桌面探索者的话
其实挺久之前就已经加到了愿望单里面了
结果加略者点悬案米
平时看到捆绑包里面才看到的
然后其实评价要比那个桌面探索者要更高
一点
小鲁特里感觉会略有折磨了
还好吧
其实鲁特里玩的还是挺贪心的
鲁特里教英子
哎
谢罗已经谢罗已警的人俏
谢谢叶风的人翘
谢落星成名的人翘
谢谢乐死谢音乐的五五到五点二星光铃铛
谢谢谢谢
七月
赵天星的粉色灯牌和人气票
谢谢谢谢
刘和先流核桃物
删掉一点五星泡泡
其实这个哦玄案好像之前也有人推荐过
可以了
谢刘河
谢六合都五升到二十福林
享受恭喜东西
谢你的无删掉二十福利小受和
谢谢你的二十删掉十好运右业和二十三到
二十点八星
光铃铛
有时七月上天星的人翘
刚刚不是有人说是重置版吗
听不懂的奴特里翻译过来
本身也比较难记
谢谢谢张星星的人气票
谢谢烤魔怪
谢谢卡魔怪的粉色灯牌
谢谢帕里斯帕老的五神到五点星光铃铛
谢谢啊嗯驱散瑕疵的粉色灯牌谢飞鸟
小纯的粉色灯牌谢零写零一的女生好看
现在她九二五五的粉酸灯牌
谢谢无破谢无珀的水晶鞋
谢谢你的水晶鞋
谢谢狮子的白色幽尾梦的呃
人翘写七月
赵天星写七月赵天星的五三到5点二星光
铃铛谢不破
谢无破的人气票
谢午和
而且五和试肢傲耐想的粉碎灯泡先示安的
粉色灯泡的
人气票写音响写音响你就好看
谢谢
嗯
繁昌的应变是谁
粮票的广告想到了一饿就肉爆一搜
你就向外卖领红包
米家的粮票是牲口
是牲口
但是一饿肉就肉包吃
嗯
好
等一下啊
电脑好像配好了
嗯
一搜你真相
嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯
看到这个很难不下的
明天先去把游戏打开
稍等好了
隔壁的画面先弄出来
这这个对了
电脑倒计时两天
电脑初步装好了
要夸夸锤屏
是的
实质损在就快能复活了
不过不急吗
谢谢冰布洛芬
谢谢冰布洛芬的流星雨
晚上好
咕咕坠顶哦
是这样
是这样读的吗
还没有换直播
已经呃已经弄好了
已经配好了
还没有去领他回家
呼声虽是呼辜
但那个这个字的话
它本身有孤和瓜的两个读音吗
来了开始吧
萨利者的悬案
看看是什么样的故事啊
哦听到了关车门的声音
这窗子是封起来了的
嗯
抽宅店宅店的窗窗子是封起来了的哦
这边有个报纸
什么周日环抱吗
看一眼哦
周日环报佳丽宅体新鲜尸体到底发生了什
么
上周日
一座废弃的乡间别墅内发现了多名男女的
遗体
然后首批抵达现场的目击者描述到呃一个
面部朝向在
倒在台台阶上的男性遗体血迹斑斑
呃
据目击者所说
还有屋内还有更多遗体
具体数量尚未确认
就是看到了门口的就直接先去报案了
是吗
而且均推测为近期死亡
然后警方就只公布了其中一名遇难者的身
份
是当地的工匠
约翰霍布斯
他的前妻和儿子都已接受问询
就是这一家就只只死了这一个工匠
看样子
但是他前妻和儿子都不知道这个霍布斯先
生
这个约翰为什么要到这个别墅来
然后尸体是由一小群忧戏重重的灯忧心忡
忡的当地居
民发现的
他们在这周日的角周日环保
哎
三月十四号十四号嗯
他们嗯他们去这个宅点的原因
至今无人知知晓
而且是一小群哦
就不排除他们也是集合一起要去干嘛的
因为死在里面的也是一群不知道什么原因
啊
但是他不是佳丽一家的吧
看起来是嗯没有什么关系的一些人
他们所所述的内容细节
包括呃譬炉内烧毁的照片
一个损坏的玩偶呃
以及破碎的彩色玻璃窗
然后受害者中至少有一人
至少有一人还是这种模式
至少有一人曾遭受枪击令
有一人可能是坠落致死
但尽管如此
警方还没有把任何人列为案件的进一步调
查对象
但是因为现在还没有其他目击者现身
关于这个案子的信息还十分有限
好
其他的就没有什么东西了
谢谢巫婆的粉钻灯牌
房租很低了吧
还有人会租吗
谢谢巫婆的粉碎灯牌
谢与风俱进的粉钻灯牌
等一下
明天再挪一下位置
到底发生了什么发生了什么呢
slocked
嗯
这是我们的声音哦
本身门是关上的
看了一下啊
锁了一下
嗯
开了一下
发现是锁着的
然后我们说完所学的
他就开了什么情况
这个伞吃对头这些还能拿吗
这个插头露在外面
总感觉不太好进去了
谢恐龙怪的心动时刻
嗯
踢电聊七七
这两边都是低电量啊
就是转动云盘嗯充电吗
好像是重叠
充电之后呢
呃现在好像笔记本啊
这个这这个是真的
想起卢特里一家了
好怕哦
都没有了手
放在显示屏上清洗 a bacon 哦
他说了瑞娅我们是瑞娅好
拿到了权限卡
然后我们是干嘛要打卡吗
哈哈
谢谢皮皮鲁泡泡龙的粉丝灯牌哦
我们长这样
ID 是七十二零二零一一年二月二十七
号回来的签
发的那现在就十二月二十二零一一年二月
二十一号
二十七号楼
这事件是在二零呃
一九三六年好多好多年以前的
多少年以前的
有人算算吗
十5年前
好吧
嗯
looks like its
not rea
dy yet
那我们要打卡了
这是什么店里
哦
已经好了
识别插入选项卡
然后恢复先前用户的数据
嗯
等一下啊
这是所有使用该机器的人员嗯写的你会没
事的
人在扫描中就像笔记一样
嗯
i 机器不能有任何有精神病史的用户操
作
也不能由任何被判断易产生错误信念或幻
觉的用户使
用
哦
这个警告挺有意思啊
必须停止使用机器
然后 EACEEE 啊
这个需要背吗
AC 嗯 RKK 天气分享 LKKT
一
六七十一四五六七八九一四五六七八九六
七十
SF 问号问号问号
这是找规律吗
嗯
一是 a 的话
c 是十一
不懂呢开始嗯有相思
这是有什么规律吗
感觉看目前看得出来有什么规律啊
应该不是找规律的
谢谢
灵魂阳光的粉色灯牌
然后自动恢复先前用户的数据地点
至少三个代码嗯
恢复之前用户的顺数据
那我们是要找到我们是要找到一些那个一
二三四五六
七八九十十一
没办法
好像没有办法要救出来什么
哎
怎么会返回啊
目前这边也没有什么可以可以再动的了
哎
这哦人物需要校准哦
开始叫我主哇哦使用手动校准
声音好像有点刺耳啊
稍等嗯
可能声音效的声音有点大
怎么感觉没变啊
现在好像好一点了
剩余三个地点
独立地点在吗
一星哎呀哦 ok 然后 RK
你说然后 KT 还有个什么来着
客厅哦
客厅入口客厅 AC 是什么
小小路
还有一个问号
问号问号没出来啊
对的
后面是 RK
是哦
这边好了
鹌鹑哦
对啊
但是那个笔记上面还有一个笔记
上面还有个 SF 队
当时说沙难道是沙发吗
一天在想那个是科幻小说
顺丰还行
书房啊哦那没事的哦
嗯哼客厅书房
那还有卧室来试试看啊
卧室
哎
主卧呢
顺丰是人能想到的
没有
哎
厕所
厨房厨房总得有吧
对的
厕所或者浴室摄影棚应该不会有
毕竟他们又不是这里
不是米汀家呃
浴室
哎
算了
他有可能不是因样这样命名的
还真的这么菜
这样不好
我们先走吧
卧室
我们刚刚不是超了吗
呃
不是超了还行
试了吗
这个房子确实会感觉会有车库啊
试试看
没有是的
还是按这个继续吧
哦
我们现在我们是要猜每个人是在哪个地方
吗
现在备忘 ok 了
嗯嗯
这两个人这两个人在这里
这两个在厨房不对吗
印象中 AC 是一和十一啊
这是通过了还是说错了呀
通过了还是说错了呀
但是按理来说
一在哪一个都有可能了哦
二一然后十一是这样吗
嗯
零一 AC 十一
哎
是这样吗
看一下哦
前面还真的有
前面有时间线零 AC 一十一哦
这样吗
世界咸疑
时间线已哇哦鹌鹑小鹿开始了
原来头开头还有一个下一个汽车引擎
工鸣能看见冥冥中神转
do dont think
stock 人物
人物一说到卡住了
你能使劲推一下吗
他是死机啊
嗯我还是动不了车子卡死
我也没办法
十一号是在帮忙推车的
这位 plus the jump
thing
wash this weather
现在外面也在下雨
你 come back
tomorrow
what is like like
helps 是对了
没劲
鲁伯特和鲁伯特有关系有关系
m 不要
你这是来做客还是干嘛的
you follow me
男
问 p 生 the house is
他们决定
直接走过去
i just that 鲁特里皮啊
他是不是鲁特里吗
哦
鲁伯特哦
对了啊
不好意思
这样是不是长得有点像
不然就 forget it 看不热
这个所以这个像管家一样的点啊
这个是被邀请过来的人
do you have a
number ab
out the guess
without t
he city
im sure what they
are
nice to remember
特鲁伯特之内谢谢你
i receive the
limitatio
n earlier this
week
哦
说到请柬过来看的
for whatever
reason i d
ecided to come
anyway
看样子应该是最家里类的人
its a privilege
to be
a guest in galley
house
能成为在宅底的宾特是种荣幸
这个他很以自己的工作为行啊
write to us at the
top
of those steps is
entra
nce to the house
miits knock and
misr
是到刺的种
看起来被请过来的
说不定会生气
如果说你背起来是是是荣幸这种话的话
空车一段时间了哦
时间线一明白
这个是可以随时回来再看的那就到这边来
哦
邀请函拿到了
我们先把第二个弄好吧
哎
怎么二二的话是一六七十入口
谢林音的 EBC 以荣幸开名啊
嗯下一个萨母
哎
嗯 i music excuse
me 啊
这是个其思 me 买那度哦
一个我也不舒服啊
他 no
hello
物流网六号楼
i i mockiy
这是刚刚过来哦
这是佳丽吗
六号是佳丽
十号是因个是号女生在找香子
完了我们还没看呢
七号来了
这是艾迪加里艾利认识哇
有东西掉落地里
他住在这里
但是他不认识鲁伯特家里
呃
你说的对
我们该静下脾气
呃
然后十一管家免得之后又忘记记了
哎
管家不让我们哦
然后蛇不舒服
女云桑找桑谁来着
胸盾老乡
然后六佳丽
然后但是叫艾等是吗
哎呀
天呐
好难记啊
名字
然后 i 听还可以直接在游戏界面编辑
等一下过去的
哎
得他那他到底吃不吃那个谁来着
怎么 a 找不出来啊
嗯这字读什么啊
尘埃爱 d 没错呀
抽扩好扩张吧
七号说小维女人哎呀
没有同意啊
目前有这些人
那娃娃摔碎了
想办法让你妹妹冷静些
嗯
看看可以在人身人身上吧
是吗
哦
还真是啊
你谁呀
你这是在香顿哦
家里 ID 称爱的 IID
然后小维是
然后这个小维是试过姐姐
嗯
小维让放一号进来
一号签
说是司机好了嗯
没否认劝过
应该说他说他自己就是了
但是他没有听说过
摩鲁鲁伯特是鲁伯特吗
娃娃摔碎了
好
然后邀请函这边是签的约翰
那我们这边是约翰了
这是约翰来着
那应该就是新闻里面的那个约翰约翰缘恨
不是叫约翰
什么来着
约翰霍布斯
对
但虽然也可能是血鬼啊
我不是
然后听过你和克莱尔的事
克莱尔是他前妻吗
看样子蛇
然后是他的生日
讲的是这边是罗伯特家里
嗯
我们当然都没有您的天赋
好
那可以直接复制吗
哦
是的
哎
不管了
现在先这良你谁啊
你啊
然后时间线一是明白
那我们到三去了三的话是四五六七八哦
三四五六七八好像是九号在不在啊
不太记得了
看一眼好像没有就好
有就好
那就全部都出场
完了
除了二号和三号之外哦
选错了客厅嗯
客厅比预想中的要更窄
没有啊啊
is if with you no
微波
什么六次弹了5号技术衣服
i am sorry
is that so much to
hang
my coat
who is this man
apparently his car
got
stuck in the mud
on qua
e lane
这一部分每天就不念了
毕竟有本事很配音
its fine
ih tell you later
he brought a all
let ch
aampaign with him
嘘
well
i should hope you
weren
t counting on a
hospit
ality
四号还在听清楚 my names
john hohobs
i actually
received an
invitation to come
here
from a man called
pet
galley
has anyone
至少目前其他人还认识吗
哎
关注久的那个人说
never by that make
ttin
g afraid
都说没听过这个名字啊
没被
so sorry
theres evidently
been
some sort of
mistake
dont worry about
it
youre welcome to
stay
here as long as
you nee
d
哦
这么大方
this is victoria
helen
tony
eddy and danian
回到他就是小微
应该开始 the evening
did you have
anything p
lanned mother
because we really
shoul
dnt start until
my dau
ghter arrives 马 sh
marh
should we come me
anyti
me soon
excuse me and does
anyo
ne know where any
is
but she said she
didnt
want to come
i dont see why we
all
need to be here
and i pick your
pardon
拜拜
how are you
actually mu
thoer
i might need to
stay th
e night walve
这是吗
小
if you wout mind
at least i was
invited
here
i suppose we could
acco
mmodate one more
ill show you to
the sp
are bed in the
study
and you welcome
with a
studenion
we could do with a
stro
ng man to help
sethings
那一起走的就是达米 IS 哦
八号
你是达米安
sounds perfect 玛莎达
米安
could you follow
me to
the billid room
please
维多利亚 like a
private wor
d
哇哦不过还要分配照片吧啊啊呃这是五号
五号是刚才的玛啥
是我刚才是我号吗
有点记
记不清他的名字了
你要看看对打妈啥说的这是谁
这是谁
这是谁和这是谁
然后打米安
打米安说他阿米安大面怎么八号是达米安
然后维多利亚是小维
等一下去分配
我们先弄完这边吧
然后海伦托尼艾迪艾迪我们已经分好了哦
在我女儿来之前就应该是托尼
对
猜一下
这个应该是头鸟
然后另外剩下剩下一个女生应该是嗯啊不
对
这有可能是托尼亚达米安托尼
应该是男的对海伦唯一一个女生
另外还剩一个女生是几号来着
气反了吗
哦
这一个这个是男生
那就是托尼弄弄个弄
这个九号是那个女生吗
弄女生的话是嗯海伦 ok 指甲分分配
完了走
我要看这边嗯看一眼
嗯
同遗产纠纷案
一部分是呃遗产纠纷案
一部分是那个加佳丽宅地的
why 这玩法这个玩法和那个卢特里一
家真的是一
样的声音
可以听一下哦
能能听声音的
原来哦这里是至少有一位死于枪枪支哦
手写性命列表
换选鱼有蔬菜痕迹之后
怕是管家哦度哦
轮椅使用者羊戴着婚戒
礼服上有红酒字
狐狸用胶卷盒和一把钢琴钥
使左腿长期受伤
嗯
啊你把鹅呢这血血液酒精浓度偏高
嘴部周围有可可饮料的痕迹
喝了酒还喝可可挺能喝啊
喝了这么多酒还喝 coco 浓烈的香
水味
缺少一枚戒指
路上有灰烬
ok 哦
就是坠落的这就是约翰了
只能是约翰了
对
邀请函从高处坠落就是吗
这未遇的难者是在门口在台阶上
ok 云雀鼹鼠是被勒死的
就一个女儿
而且有个人那个有一份遗嘱水塔
有烟草痕迹
随身携带有一块怀表和一一张征兵宣传宣
传单啊
好疼哦
体格强壮
随身携带有黑色汽车的钥匙
与渡丫一起发现这下面这个达米安楼与狗
鱼一起发现
怀孕早期有微弱的薰衣草香气
就是猫莎
这个是打米恩吗
难道不知道燕子中枪三次哦
他和和谁呀
死于强行轰化
都说死于枪击的还有皮手套和一把带血的
匕首
然后就是一个巨大的金属钥匙
一张叠好的五人家族素描红鼠狼
右手有烧伤痕迹
揉后了一些酒
口袋里发现一枚戒指
手手里握着一条项链
口袋里发现一个戒指
之前谁找了个戒指来着
刺猬黄鼠狼拿的刺猬的戒指吗
哈哈
这首之前那个机器的样子
我们现在用机器好像要更高级一点了
好了
看完了
然后呢我们现在能做什么
在书房里面书房里面的话
应该是想一想啊
我们有一号和那个达米安和玛莎三个人什
么呀
好吧
嗯
变了是还有三个问号日
刚刚看了剧情
知道他们几个人过来了吗
临时航线 is he is it
right
嗯
啊直接发现了尸体了吗
哎啊
so sorry
我把把酒砸了
have you checked
for ap
plse
直接在这边发现了谁的尸体啊
二号或者三号的
but hes
definitely dea
d
甚至上面都没有数字
oh
first stranger
times ti
mes up the door
next
another is found
dead i
n the study
do you know
this month
i certainly do not
and i cant fathem
how
we could have
entered t
he house without
someon
e letting me know
这这里不是 consign the
physi
cal injuries given
age
i say
hot failure most
likely
well sasomething
right
瑞蕾
a strangeman
sneaking a
round our house
害我你就 believe ved 那
马
莎莎加丽也就玛莎和 AD 输了
哇
有些人剩一家子龙居然是他们家的吗
program for a
piano itt
le
嗯
has anyone heard 钢
琴
a million wes 阿米利亚
not a composed
arrive at of 是嫌那个作
曲吗
hopes he wouldnt
have
anything to do
with it
刚才有有一个有钢琴什么都弄过
but if ive
arrived at
a bad time
im sure i could
find s
omeone else to
stay non
sense
mister hobs will
saw th
is out in the
meantime
perhaps it would
be wis
e to keep this
between
ourselves 这面照嘞
would you fetch
thone t
on case
香盾十号不是在找香盾来着
moufuly sh
ry about the boss
tle
its the list of
my wor
ries
john
what are your name
why dont you come
thro
ugh to the dining
room
with me
it should be empty
我才不行
不是电影风头四三的牌
那我们可以查一下餐厅喽
这边结束了哦
我们是我们先添加吧
好了
然后看看这里有什么线索
岁鸟是一个词
甜滋滋伟大
跟我说什么娃娃摔岁了
不知道讲的是什么
我不知道会不会有可以之后再看看嗯
信息能找到更多三顿
三顿在厨房来着
这个能算吗
哦
看看外面客厅是说的客厅吗
但是客厅已经有吧吧已经有了吧
客厅已经很早就有了
对
嗯
知道桑顿
桑顿等一下会被喊到厨房去
呃
但是不知道桑顿是几号
哎
十号肯定不是桑顿
十号是在找桑顿
然后达米啊
维多利亚塞 i 迪玛莎等一下玛莎呃
达米啊和桑顿会在厨房可以看一下
这边呢已经到我们客厅了
看看这边有没有什么嗯女儿过来
我觉得他一时半会儿过不来了海伦的女儿
啊
然后还有一个叫安妮的
先不穷举吧
主要是你穷举了
你也不知道对不对
反而有可能会影响到判断呢
台球室这里有个台球
试试看这个台球好像只能两个哦
台球找到了
台球室会有谁来着
海龙和艾迪海伦和艾迪一起过去了
托尼和维多利亚又去了一个单独的什么地
方吗
托尼和维多利亚哎
维多利亚他最后说话是在哪离开此处
但是不知道呀
然后这边是书房
书房我们找到了线索
可以去书房
哎呀
嗯想做是不是该做一下笔记啊
看一下添加一下
嗯
先去台球室试试吧
这个先去报警
那玛莎达米安和桑顿
但关键是不知道桑顿是几号呀
难道只能穷举吗
先看看啊
之前有个过河宫崎有关的书
这个狐狸左腿长期受伤
虽说携带一个空箱卷壶
我钢琴钥匙可能是先看
但是怎么看呢
台球社
我们台球室就只知道有达米安
然后还可能有香盾
然后到时候嗯那个谁也要过去
谢谢
我两过我在的粉钻灯牌情趣还不少
总说达米安汤面在哪
玛莎应该也会过去
但是他有可能会带着那个香盾先过去
相对应该是男生十一号
是管家十一号
我们还没给他名讲名字
他应该不会是在找十一号吧
十号在找十一号吗
我先试试
关键是时间线
不一定是这样的
是时间线
等一下等一下
哎
等一下
他刚刚试了
说了要去
他就是吗
哦
这是餐厅去餐厅去餐厅台球社是另外两个
人
关键是哈哈
关键是时间线要怎么选呢
三个是这是另外两个
那这个不是三吨
那这个呢十一号是香盾
是管家吗
不舍推是可能数字是错的
艾莎可能一起去了
妈莎和正去餐厅
他不去餐厅的
马上让那个就在书房等着的呀
哦哦
是抹上去
就嗯但是我把桑桑顿叫来明白气婚了
八号不去
达完你当年去好
终于说错四川话有吗
now john tell me
why yo
ure here 直接打刀给他看吗
its not quite
what i w
as expecting
i received this
invitat
ion
那往回走
看去 it would make
那比如说台球室的那个时间线该选哪个
该选二还是该选三呢
i dont like the
ton of
this
im afraid ive
never h
eard of a rupet
galli
could he be a
distant r
elative
he is unlikely to
be
i wasnt born a
ali
i only two
所以是你叫马上家里
it would have been
arou
nd the time i
moved int
o this house
i suppose whats
open y
ou might be able
to she
d some light on
why
im in
we were just
having a s
mall gathering
here ton
ight
i think adaddy
must hav
e organized it
i teaca ay ys
prinand f
amily
though i dont
know why
we suddenly have
stran
gers turning up
嗯
嘿很 well
谢谢
they were ten of
us in
the house
not counting
whoever we found
in the
study
oh
and theres
daunten
of course
that makes eleven
heis
albutt and our
only mem
ber of stuff 哦
桑顿确实是管家
one of the most
know so
mething surely
whats t
hat you hold in
john
i found near the
body t
hought it probably
was
one of yours
i was thinking
maybe someone else
migh
t recognize 另外一个是应
该是女孩张
宁
i havent been
there in
a long time 啊
well
thats something
is loo
king to
i suppose now
教堂里
i coch
could you gotta
take it
to a buta
hell be dealing
with t
he the mess in the
stud
y
哦
是美
i think matti
millia
ill go there now
他居然有教堂
and you welcome to
个一家宅
顶里面有个教堂
unbelievable 是大户人家
等一下十一号香炖
然后十号等等
这里是其他人都在客厅口子
其他客人都在客厅这里
然后这里还有个衣服
现所以现在有个衣服
有个安妮
然后还有个谁
还有个嗯小维的妹妹
有可能是安妮
有可能是伊芙
这两个的话还有一个人
你看这里三号时间线的时候
海伦喊艾迪去一下台球室
那我们应该选四吗
还是选三呢
艾迪和海伦的话先试试三啊嗯应该是行哎
呦
写菠落豆包的
等一下那哎呦呦呦有的有个迷关 OK
出现了
i didnt want to
make a
scene of it eddy
but i dont expect
you
to lose track of
my dau
ghter and act
so csisure is she
she ran off
somewhere
thats not good
enough
if youre right
shes fine
we were in here
earlier
if she just had my
pa d
rink k dughter has
not
a drunk my
daughter
i didnt we just
had a
small argument
i think she was
upsaid
like like i did
shjust
had to drink
if youre
wondering why
she took it so
badly
then you have have
to a
sk yourself takes
some
responsibility for
once
if she upset and
think
think you dont
know th
at she
she a drink
naturally
i would have
ggoing a l
ook for her
but then that
strange m
antn over the
daughter
and alright
i didnt buy you
and en
gage the dream 结婚字
get about my
daughter
我给你买结婚戒指
what are you
looking fo
r
its nothing 才是挑借战
原来 we lost the
ring
but i know its in
hear
someone excuse II
don
t undercontrol
she lost it
just as that was a
knoc
k at the front
door
and i have another
chan
ce to look it yet
you would better
find i
t
then you tell her
your
thrw 房房 never
happen ag
ain
do you understand
me
yes
mrs hour 倒准儿大尔海伦
ruing a perfectly
happy
engagement eddy 好信
道儿
这个这个这个这个还轮到了嗯 OK
然后海轮到了就是艾迪
然后佳丽他没有否认
感觉应该确实是新佳丽
那所以那个玛莎是他妈妈艾迪的妈吗
刚才好像喊的爱的龙看一眼
嗯
他刚刚被邀请过来的时候
还有桑顿
桑顿
我们之前已经试了 i 登 m 就是艾
迪哦
是他的历称那边是确实没有看到有奖呃
他应该在书房
让我们去让约翰去书房找艾顿那过去一趟
吧
我们先应该是漏了
哎
好难弄香顿
呃
达米羊会在吗
因为他让我达米安带回来的
不知道是不是只有他们两个人
小鬼书房倒了
嗯
马上可能是艾迪的妈妈就感觉啊
hello
again
good evening 4
the room should be
fit
you to stay in
tonight
甚的还敢在这里吃 moment
哎
外面雨太大了
没办法
II am 笑率百般
not a problems 拿着走
你的节目
像看电视剧演还好
没有
觉得很慢很大
turn it up at the
wrong
time can be helps
on
and youre always
welco
me in gali house
这管家的职业素养真好感觉十号应该是那
个感觉
十号应该是那个女儿
他那喝了酒之后不爽
然后找找再找管家没找到
and then open and
cloth
es again
i presume one of
them m
ost for you
就是他进门了之后
还有人进来吗
顿时感觉像是女孩 closed
for a s
econd time
a guest arrived in
the
kitchen 来了
truth in rather
inibiat
ed
but nothing out of
the
ordinary 这个厉害
around the time
the bottle smashed
a se
cond guest
arrived in the
kitchen
摔摔瓶子四号是放时间线的时候
and informed me i
was n
eeded here
马赛克先生
马赛克打秒游戏
three of us knew
about
the body
oh
i almost forgotten
hes a key i found
earl
ier
math asthmidtivity
马赛克应
该是那个达米安达米安把他找过来的
sit t pocket
you dont mean
rupid 改为
do you
yes
paul
mister gally 啊
he used to visit
the ch
apel
often said
哎
他吃了萝萝
他 i ive met 加盐
what is a
mysterious ou
s man
this rupet gallly
let so many
i know ws we is
could you show me
to wi
n
im terribly sorry
ce DT
我我跟大一些骂联不行
去一顿每
yes
刚才死了那个 past away
youll do best to
give
the key to oswell
if you see him
now i am sorry es
but 这个管家一直都在喊信
喂
i need to ask you
但是我们现在分不清楚谁是谁的姓
one of
the
the other erpt
是啊
看来是刚刚死的
那个我的天呐
谢谢谢谢好多等一下
我们要先把达米安的信加上去
妈塞可好像是要这个吗
哦
嗯对的
嗯
第一次是临近门掉第二个这门
第二次关上之后有没有扣
我的人来到了厨房
他看起来醉的厉害
但是他说的是客人啊
说是客人
如果说佳丽家的时候
呃
自己人辛佳丽的那两个就是玛莎和艾迪是
自己人的话
他的未婚妻会算作客人吗
第二位客人呃
有位客人
然后第二位客人来来到厨房
然后他离开后
第二位客人离开了之后
在这他在照料第一位那个醉酒的客人
然后马赛克过来了
跟他说
我跟他说需要来这里哦
是那个客大号
大号不管了
认得出来就行了吧
是哪个塞啊
感觉复制一下比较好啊
嗯
等一下马赛克对的哦
这刚才找到的钥匙
马上让我交给你刚才找到的钥匙哦
就是从佳丽口袋准是从佳丽先生的口袋里
面划出来的
他以前经常去教堂
说以前你刚才没认出来吗
哦
见到奥斯瓦尔德
最好把钥匙交给他嗯嗯
记录一下
那这个是什么的钥匙啊
教教堂的钥匙吗
为什么要交给他呀
写溜烟写在弄死全灯盘
嗯
教堂我们之前已经说了
右墙的哦
对
这是教堂的钥匙
若还有谁会经常去教堂吗
这是十号
他在哪儿待着呢啊
我难受死了啊
我得他只刑警酒是吧
所以他去厨房了
应该是嗯十号这个是在时间线二
那时间线三的时候嗯
十号十号和桑顿应该在厨房见面了
我们试一下
有新的证据
但是等明天先先试一下
三号开始说话
见面了吗
耶水岁性的声音厨
他在厨房做事
harry
hurry
good evening
miss 到了 if you don
t my
mising
im not in mu dry
i 叫 t coo OI 叫什么 o
了 o
co OOO
他还在称呼他的客人哦
热可可
no
im a bit busco
if you like hot
coco
应是是锅
he he doeslolove
me
im you
you 给他再给他咬糖
the think XI loves
me
but he doesnt
really 他
自以为爱我
但是我只是一个被爱的对象吧了
yes
lucky
i have you
dont let him
forget it
youre becoming
looking
for you
anytime too
im sure 人去 very 吧
这边是 runaway
不去不去
看 with 厉害啊
differenrence or
somewh
ere like that
you know
and eat always
isisand
sit on the beach
嗯
真厉害
my voice is in
france
i wouldnt know mr
dow
but if you send me
a po
stcard once yorkay
they could let me
know
cant you
他确实厚大
哎
我嘞个 my marry
maybe i me
你带什么 ID 的话
还叫什么四个男字叫度蜜月啊
he is your 好 QQ
thanks
siari
i still hate him
though
of course
let me know if
theres
anything else you
need
misr r
and ill be happy
to he
lp 还一个空调
如果他是那个的话
等一下我们先看看 helen
helen 的女
儿是吧
衣服就是马上衣服跟你在一起吗
这人是谁
我看看呃海伦等一下啊
海伦顿尔桑顿也叫到尔来着
哦
不对
不是顿顿在他的女儿叫道道
那个道尔对香顿是哈瑞机毁了
有人知道安妮在哪了
那时候应该是衣服了
嗯
是的
这应该是衣服
嗯
闲鱼衣服还挺还挺唏嘘的
相对哈利
然后应该差不多了
那二号和三号
其中一位是安妮
还有一位是嗯嗯
看看要不要试试贴照片
怎么贴照片啊
哦
这里还有一个第二页没看哦
这个是在教我们啊霍布什啊
霍布斯二十六在前门台阶上
就是他最后的死亡地点呢
植物那儿可以选形象
什么我看一眼哦
还真是就就是那个光头嗯
二号不知道丝毫不确定
枪盾巨大的精神是
其实感觉有可能是他嘞
等一下选
先把那个我喝可可的鹅放上去了
然后这个是鹅他吗
缺少页面戒指
他不会是把自己的戒指给了别人吧
手里握着一糖哦
对
原来是他十一号
原来管家这么年轻呃
达米马赛克拿断判断的线索不够啊
拿着一瓶苦艾酒还不知道轮椅使用者附近
的照片上有
两个名女孩判断出来谢过敏和清空的粉色
灯牌
就钢琴钥匙
钢琴钥匙
礼服上有红酒字
带着婚戒
此事仅为一女
她妈妈怕是年纪没有这么大吧
这不会是海伦吧随身携带有与狗鱼这两个
一起发现的
再看一下吧
嗯
现在还判断不出来
总感觉这个黄鼠狼可能是可能是哎得可能
是因为他最
后他最后找到了戒指之类的女儿是第三排
哪个
你说哪个女儿
对
只能说可能酒精含量偏血液
酒精含量偏高
就看之后他有没有喝酒了
来
我们先看看
不知道跑哪了
远处传来酒瓶碎裂声
酒瓶碎裂声之后来了第二位客人
来我们看一下之前的描述啊呃是在这里哦
但也没什么奇怪的酒
酒瓶碎裂之后
第二位客能来厨房
而且是个男生
然后他离开之后
然后马赛克才过来
那就是呃这个地方四摔裂的时候
那倒是差不多
那就是4的时候过来的吗
嗯
孙翁也在
当时那先看看四的时候
还是在厨房
有这两个人
以及一位男的有位男生看看是不是痛过呀
不是同尼
然后也确定了
不是海问那个不是达米安
也不是艾 d 艾迪艾 d 当时应该是
在台球室
达米安是后面过来的
最后过来的
就是中间还有一位阔人
在四的时候
应该是等二或者三不是啊
那二可能是安妮嗯
二三那二就是安妮啊
哎
这里是已经确定了吗
这个是还没确定吗
为什么有一边显示的
对呀
人物三
what brings you
after a
fter dinner
i you you IH you
you th
e dinner
哦
他的爸爸
那这个是个年纪很大的吗
哦
所以这个就是那个谁谁谁是谁名字很长的
i know i have a
look af
ter dindinner
i 有可能没有做其他的 live 五
个 s 那
这个至少能确保他5人觉要什么时候5个
那这个 s 个五个词
find it as soon as
my n
eighbor telling
what yo
u told me harry
about t
he job
i dont know what
your
e talking about
mr
a i dont know any
笑堂
i couldnt be
repeating
was this
your father must
told y
ou something
no doubt
well
sr
i suppose i did
hear ab
out a few things
it was the one to
bury
her
that was
he know
低保是爱他爸 found found
boac
hty kyou 没吗
没事
you do well not to
spea
k of such matters
in th
is house
ya lady
im terribly sorry
so youll be kind
dific
ult for all being
a lit
tle unusual this
evenin
g 教堂
什么事啊
i run the style
ill had my dinner
on e
veryone else is
left th
e dining room
im the search
of course
and do i apologize
abou
t the key
well
没听到你 you first
i dont trust the
owner
s of this house to
know
what to do with it
im sure ive just
misp
laced it
so and if you
forgive m
e for saying it
i think shes
happy to
see you backs
am i 你说我吗
你在说什么
dont mean
anything bah
还去死
hes earearly 里是他在说
鬼吧
见到鬼什么的
just thought you
should
know so that
forgive m
e
father the step
your ou
th
you finance to
bring to
me
and then neither
review
will mention this
agai
n
of course
搁置 that will be al
五六六六
六六六不知道到底发生了什么
但是呢把这个很复杂的名字
不知功血奥斯瓦尔德奥斯瓦的选个老头儿
哪个老头儿铲除
感觉气质会和这个比较像一点
会是吗
也不知道啊
气质要更香一点
就你了老头
然后这里还有个安妮喽
安妮拿着钥匙
嗯
但是那个巨大的钥匙不一定是哦
对哦
他拿到的巨大钥匙
可能就是教堂的钥匙
他们最后把钥匙拿给他了
安妮是米天神
小安妮是谁家的啊
你说 hurry
衣服跟你在一起呢
没有带到另外一个人过来看一下啊
这个是那个这是鹅
有人知道安妮在哪吗
安妮和达里安
然后托尼说
他说他不想来
那我目前就这些了
小维的妹妹
但维多利亚还不知道他的
还不知道维多利亚的姓是什么
来
我们先来看看那个吧
先看看线索吧
第二页管家在哪
管家一在一些二在厨房
三也在厨房
这个我们知道
然后这个是台球
台球是呃这个都是我们已经推出来了的
只是他现在又给了提示
然后前门台阶
前门台阶的话
是门口吗
还是前门呢
祸不死二十六
那一共就是二十六了
先看看你有没有钱的
嗯
能否还是就是在这个啊入口
那就是入口好慢啊
这个这个真的很难赚
哈哈哈哈
这个真的很难穿
这个真的很难转
因为你按你按下去了之后
你不知道你的鼠标在哪哦
往右边就行了
那没事嗯
和约翰
你这车迷走吧
是的
原来左右拉就行
小说怎么说啊
走走引导啊
那游戏厉害
嗯
天花铃声感觉就不是个坏人
有点惨
谢在立法者送花花
嗯
游戏名字在屏幕下方有电话铃声
这里有一个线索算是
然后二十六确定了
我们先看看这里啊
这里呃桑顿和哈瑞都离开了 SF 是哪
来着
书房都离开了书房
他们本身是在这个地方录的
然后嗯那桑顿他现在要去哪个地方呢
在打扫碎玻璃
但是离开了这离开了这会往哪去呢
啊
他去厨房吗
把尸频脱去时
厨房有点有点地狱的吧
那只能我们再继续吧
我们再继续
厨房应该还有一个时间线在4之后
呃
在我的时候
对
在我的厨房
在我的厨房有香顿和和这个大米安不喜欢
他又过来了
继续看
在那个老老老老东西
哈哈啊
老登西走了之后
thhnton is it
yes
喵喵这个 me
i dont think weep
md d
ammy micsql
some things
happened up
stairs
martha asked me to
let
you know
we heard the
bottle sma
sh room down here
is ev
erything
all right
its worse than
just a
bottle 啊
someones die
那岂不是 yourself 这个也听
到了
到衣衣服
i dont know
i dont recognize
him h
ow many people are
in t
his house
天天
so let me see you
shoul
d recognize our
two hos
ts
so it wont be
other of
them
then there are
eight gu
ests
including yourself
and
misstyle over
there
and theres myself
of course
有 show his dad
as i thought
this is someone
else
我以为谁是假的
you want to go and
look
its up in the
study
哦
他去看了吗
yes
ghost 啊啊
我退别着了
could you look
after mi
ster wour for me
if you take her
over to
emens room
i think she
probably al
l to lie down and
make
sure not to run
into an
yone else
least of adadam 去姆
房间
但是别遇到姆
那为什么不去其他人的房间啊
感冒男
lets get you up 哦
果然站前就有了
又 very 子
im going to take
you t
o your bed
if thats alright
with
you
beddy doesnt
deserve m
e anyway 哦
嗯带他去艾德梦的房间吗
注意别撞到其他人
尤其是埃德蒙先生
埃德蒙先生爱德姆 who 来挑个什么
憨森的十大
米安
谁要算了
可根本就猜不出来他的审美啊啊艾德姆哦
对对对
吵架的啦啦啦啦啦啦
行行行
行行爱的梦
等一下
我没给艾德 m 换衣服来着
当米好贵
海底来给你加上
免得免得等一会儿又不认识了
笑死艾丽摔的
我们逆称
好的好的
就是看看吧
现在看看
然后我们是在五的时候
但是送你回床上休息的话用哦
我接下来是这两个人
伊芙和马赛克去哪个地方呢
卧室没有出现啊房间房间艾迪的房间呢嗯
还真是啊代
t 的房间嗯嗯
行
艾迪的房间是在六嗯
是吧
嗯
hello
AT 的房间啊
嗯嗯嗯哎
will you be
alright by
yourself
什么意思
i want my brother
他弟弟还有一个哦
那我感觉觉 tony 是他弟弟了
dont let anyone
else i
n here
in the meantime
understand there
are st
rangers in the
house
oh
recognize his noke
you
stay for a bit
wouldnt you
哎
i think you ought
to tr
y and get some
sleep 哦
i dont want you
为什么你跟我说过你的事
did she say nice
things
about 小维师的他
yes
谢谢
she said
you have quite a
charm
about you
and she said
eddy is very lucky
to h
ave you
you making it up
no
she respect you a
lot
even if you dont
seem
to get on sunday
没有人剧透啊
我们本来就是在猜这个房间应该会叫什么
名字啊
i remember now she
said
you could be quite
hon
est
sometimes aldy
still th
ink about her
i can tell
我们只是在猜他的到底会怎么命名而已
im sure thats
not tru
e
哼
whats your ring
we had
not given jalia
id had too much
to dri
nk
and night
嗯嗯
i accidentally
lost it
i hope we find it
im sure he will
he car
es about you
no ah 不虚伪什么嗯
哼嗯嗯
还是 go
ill tell you
about you
here
but you should be
able
to get some sleep
befor
e he gets here
will you be right
on yo
ur own until then
所以到是两家人吗
回来还真
但是为什么哦
那直接走了
嗯
房子里有陌生人
虽在
我们要推理一下哪个是他弟弟哦
感觉是男生好像就只有托尼了
维动力啊来去看一眼这里的文字版了
小维跟我说过
你说其实你们俩关系不太好
他很尊重你哦
感觉应该是他嗯他的人太好了
不懂他为什么跟你在一起
你看起来又沉闷又严肃
还想着他谁呢
嗯嗯
那应该就只有托尼了
毕竟另外一个是他还带了香槟来
那托尼应该就是呃托尼说道而加的喽
托尼是道尔家的
然后这么说的话嘛
呃海伦应该是有一儿一女
海伦有一儿一女的话
呃
艾莎是有个儿子
然后只有一个女儿的
应该就是安妮他妈了是吧
或者说维多利亚他妈当然也有可能女儿根
本就不在了
不在现在呃
不在现场玛莎嗯
玛莎什么玛莎她是一个儿子啊
玛莎他是艾迪
他妈呀哦
不对
玛莎舍
哎
等一下有点混玛莎舍
对了
玛莎是艾 d 他吗
没错
这里能推出安尼拉了
因为啊只有一个啊
那人物照片里面啊只有一个
他说只有只有一个女儿
轮椅的那位哦
不是轮椅的那位是哪个
那这个带着婚戒
那羊就是维多利亚吗
忘记去哪儿了
哦
不对
这是维维多利亚吗
这是维多利亚
这个是那个达米安体格强壮
因为当时让他去帮忙翻东西
应该是了
等一下塞一下照片
维多利亚唯独那样是这个嗯维多利亚融嗯
哦然后再看一眼
这个应该可以写成写成你的
是安妮相关的
是托尼提到的吗
忘记了
在我女儿来这之前
就是安妮还没有到
哦
不对
不是
这个是海伦盗尔
海伦盗尔说的是衣服
有人知道安宁在哪吗
嗯
达米员当时在找安 ding 哦
安妮晚上好
晚上好
然后托尼说他不想来
他说不想来
那里是没有来的人吗
那这里是不是那个轮椅老太太啊
那就
不是安利
是安利他吗
等一下我看看啊
哎如果只有一位女儿的是这个楼
应该就是这个了
算了算了
现在时间还不还不够
我们在艾迪的房间确定了一会儿衣服
这他会喊他托尼过来
那我们六我们先去六看看
那我们刚刚是在六啊
那就是先去七托尼
嗯
这不是他们吗
难道是这两个一起过来的
哎
没有带过来
难道带的不是托尼总
可能他把艾迪带回来了吧
嗯
这边的情况是
我会告诉你弟弟在这里
不过在他来之前
你应该能睡会儿一个人待呆着没问题吧
难道是要看他一个人一会儿哦
还真的是让他一个人先呆着
一会儿
嗯
艾 y 的房间还要打呼喝了的酒
睡得很熟的样子
那雷声感觉又是一个关键时间点吗
对的
刚刚想说这个嗯咚咚咚咚咚咚哎呦
不辣条啊
我们要发电机发电了
有些好像见面也出了点问题
还是说这个游戏是这么设计的
好像是游游戏的设置
我们时间变了
机器的画风变了
然后米汀的界面下方出现一块空空白
虽然大家看到都没有区别
但是米汀这边界面变了
好像是哎
但是正面看起来有没有什么变化呀
请 one 继续吧
可能是 bug 没有显示其他东西
上面上面变了 eve
whether hell of
you bee
n maris a sleep
i could tell
listen som
ething
strange is going
on odi
d someone die
no
you
you 怎 volve
do you involve
tony
just tell me what
happe
n
not now
i need you to hold
on t
o something for me
dont tell anyone
else
about it
where did you get
it
he looks really
valuabl
e
tony 看一下很贵的东西
explain the rest
later
not just a
stranger
turned up early on
and i think hes
lookin
g for this 看起来很贵族
so 就是底不去 terney
you didnt see it
did you 不知道
just take it if 他在
厨房和艾迪
说话 edy in the
kitchen
so i should have a
it o
f time
can me know
s
vote
i told you about
him
then i 哦
还真的是那个小胡子
让我们选对沙漠鸟匙
he said his name
was jo
hn hopy
but i think osword
is u
p to something too
he and annii were
talki
ng in the attic
while the rest of
us ha
ve gathered in the
livi
ng room had now
anyis t
rying to ill
explain i
t all later
大家在客厅的时候喜欢 to your
scho
ol
remember i think
shegot
into a fight with
one
of the boys
one time
it dont matter OK
just toy of you
final
but promise me
yourself
在2时间点二还是3的时候
在在在 i promise
anything
but at least still
be a
ble to protect
myself
嗯
dont trust anyone
哈哈
这我弟弟到底身上他发生了什么来了
是在这儿吗
嗯
是三的时候
三的时候在阁楼来
我们还没把阁楼弄出来
必须哎呦
房顶直接出来了
怎么歌喽
这个小房子上面都有蜘蛛网吗
门吃呀
一声开了
oh
im sorry
sorry
i swear
it was me was tony
i told him not to
什么什么么
its a no HIH
ononi
i said i can stay
up II
IAAAA me up
sorsori
i hope you
IIIIIIAAI lo
ok sorry
i say one it
其实这个玩法那个什么 and say
sorry
i meish
i can find someone
else
to sleep if feat
for t
hat
no
thats 还速来
its nice to
revisit al
l memories
and it 那个国产的突然有点忘记
他了
四个字叫树儿
完了 it was nice to
meet
you
哦
对
一岸之声也是要推断他们的关系
几号是谁
这些那个也好
游戏
不过很久没更新了
嗯
其实什么也没做啊
哦
他是说的是托尼让他锁门了
那二号二号就是安妮和托尼在这里了
试一下啊
看样子是视频不落分的
你一开始不认识吗
有这样介绍的吗
here
what are you doing
to p
ull that is even
connec
ted to something 就
是好皮呀
这个人 you cannot be
retel
l me
al is this room is
on 加
你
but how old is the
thos
e house 这么兴奋
看官了
they went
expecting me
to turn up
this was the only
bt
they had left
feels like no one
s bee
n here for a long
time
you know what
happened
to the girl that
used t
o live here
哦哎呀
my sister told me
she s
lowly win 这
嗯
哼
they you cant
give the
betterins 就是疼你
是啊
yeah
and then one day i
don
t dont ve that i
know
jodting stop
mesing ing
哦
那个娃娃吗
都是摔下圈了吧
对
嗯
所以当时说小维你妹妹什么什么什么
sorry
and im tony if
you don
t remember me
对
就掉下去的娃娃 alright
然后他们都知道
因为是他妹妹在的房间里
所以只道是妹妹丢下来的什么的
但是至此我们也知道安妮和小维姓什么了
博隆特那维多利亚也是博隆特罗
但是他维多利亚他嫁给那个马赛克的时候
是不是要改姓啊
不管先先写在他原来的姓吧
然后看起来比较左臂有深切口
感觉是他以前嗯感觉他以前可能披萨的时
候
左臂有深切苦爱
不知道在附近村庄不一定啊
嗯
那看来不是了哦
呃等一下有两个女儿的是维多利亚和安妮
是两个女儿
那么这个附近的照片上有两名女孩还容椅
使用者
但是也不一定是他的
之前印象中有一个人的介绍是只有一个女
儿什么的哦
这个只是仅为一女
但是不是说现在的滋味
那就是说其实有一个不是他女儿之类的
有可能是本身是两个女儿
然后其中一个不是亲生的巴拉巴拉
哎
这个大胡子是谁啊
大胡子是狐狸狐狸开发的
这个是同一个人吗
认不太出来
好像胡子的茂密程度不一样
不知道了
之前有人吗
不太记得不太记得之前有人吗
那我看看啊
我们时间线二的时候
然后时间是三的时候
他没有下去客厅揉那个上来了
尤其是锁门是安妮
看到这个托托尼来的
就不想让他再进这个房间
所以才把那个房间锁上的
但是他这个地方呢又说是托尼干的
怎么做啊
我也我们也不知道他在说什么
是不想让他再进来的感觉
那我们先跟着这里走
管你是谁
觉得单纯甩个锅哦
托尼干哦
对他当时说那个娃娃丢下去了
你谁啊
你然后看来嗯让娃娃摔碎了哦
物品掉到地板上并碎裂
哦啊对了
知道是托尼丢下去了
但是我们现在我们现在应该做什么呢
台球室书房嗯
他当时到底是看到什么
稍等啊
嗯嗯
木什么什么的
现在安妮正试图干嘛
现在看不出来
那但是这里讲了呃
讲了另外两个人
那个艾 y 和 joe 应该在哪个地
方
嗯
他在厨房和艾迪说话
十三八的时候出嗯嗯
搬的时候厨房有哎
嘿埃 d 的火重
oh bloody hell
我的妹不辣挺好啊
师伯
你啊
im not great with
you
were they sorts of
thin
gs
对呀
helped me move it
outsi
de
这是弄尸体
平常 see know we was
哎呀
he had the key to
the p
antry on him
so is the 平常尝试的钥匙
谢谢千里之马
不定的粉旋灯牌
listen to me
哎
没回答
你 explain what you
re d
oing here who this
啊这么一
具尸体
no
不过 weve just
found a s
econd body
i wear
i ve told you
everythin
g
as far as i know
ive been invited
him f
or some unknown
reason
a muma died before
IID
asking why how did
you
know roopt gali
why was he here
i have no idea
i dont know know
we wa
s
and how did you
recogni
ze him
i 没认出来啊
i knew it was him
i dont know what
game
youre playing
but if this
involves an
yone of my guest
ster n
ight
then you need to
tell h
im
one member of
staff is
already been
caught up
in it
i 们就只有一个游泳吧
thats were
related
i so i thought
maybe th
e pona gave them a
righ
t
do you take me a
fool t
wo strangers in my
hous
e
and one of them
dies
i can tell someit
s goi
ng on here
i just need your
assura
nce that it wont
affec
t anyone
i should 睡了一 day
i was there at the
dini
ng room table with
ever
yone else
if someone is
behind th
is
that its some
will no
ready in the house
if t
hey brought me
here for
a reason that i
could
be endanger that
that what your
voice we
re you
但那个不一定是相对
there were two
people m
issing from dinner
one of them
well
cheese out to the
page
哦
那是在睡觉
i like 那其他人都在餐厅喽
well
i dont know who
my fat
her is
but ive never
really s
poken to mum about
it o
r giving it much
though
t
but oswald has
always b
een there in the
backgr
ound as my uncle
not that hes been
to t
his house for a
very lo
ng time
well
then perhaps you
know s
omething about
rupia ge
lly
thats a best laid
we h
ave at the moment
do you know where
i cou
ld find him
i imagine hes
waited f
or resulto leave
before
he eats
im sure you could
go i
n told dream now
thank you
dont you want to
talk
him too
我试过20小
时我们先去看看当时吃饭的情况
吧哇哇
哦那厉害
了
嗯不知道你很谢小
闹 modl 粉色灯
牌他是调了个什么东西上去
吗不会下毒了
吧血兵不用奋斗鼓鼓掌
哦液体飞剑落到滚烫的表面
上然后他被烫倒
了然后他搅拌了一下那个液
体然后带着那个液体上楼
了不会
吧可能有点阴谋论
了那刚刚吃饭的时候
呃七的时候
吗还是这个的手
吧就嗯但在切的时候应该是大家吃饭的时
候试试看
啊在餐
厅然后除了嗯除了三号不衣服之
外所有人不
对这管家除的苛刻
吧笑 no 看一眼
啊身上有可口的那个痕迹的男生看不出来
手指上有烟
草痕
迹别受到嗯烧伤痕
迹
OK 那这个就是艾迪
了这下应该可以确定这个是艾迪
了有烧伤痕迹
啊嗯还有四个人的照
片但是这里还有一二三四五六七
八还有八个
呢后八个就是玛莎托
尼托尼男生是不是不多了
呀男生一二三
啊哈
哈他是那个鹅的弟
弟那就是只能是这两
个感觉这个更 p 一
点手指上有烟草痕
迹他应该是那个水塔
吧感觉气质上这个更像是同
尼但是先不定
吧海伦岛是那个的妈
妈没有描述他坐轮
椅看起来也不是很
老
嗯而且不止英
女所以应该是这个或者这个有灰烬痕
迹缺少一枚戒
指
嗯我感觉是这个的可能性会比较大一
点
嗯然后安妮安妮的
话这两个其中一个应该是嗯然后就是玛莎
玛
莎像这个哈猜先这么猜
了我们接下来要推断吃
饭但是这里确实讲
了
嗯我一直在餐厅和其他人用
餐那难道我是在七的时
候在六的次的时
候晚餐时有两个人没来用
餐难道那个仆人他没有算在这里
面可能谢谢官咪家的免疫猫的粉碎灯
牌对他可能没有把管家设在
哦对
的他没有把仆人算在里面
嗯 please come in
and ta
ke a
seat dinner will
be up
in a
moment does it
matter it will
sitt was
nt him that you
saw w
ts it
oh
no
well i didnt
catch a g
ood
look
嗯没看清 are
damian you wouldn
t hel
p me with the
dishes fr
om the dumb
weight would you
is the
re a fine of my
daughter i believe
she
s asleep misss
dowa h
kay its up to
remind m
e of name
me afraid john
hopes i hope you
dont
my name
me you
johos i hope misr
hopes
you could do
that and sorry
about
earlier
everything i dont
know
what you talking
about what up v
you
do hope the
chinese
watch please at
it of
course how are you
liki
ng the house
mrdwa i hope this
eveni
ng hasnt been too
chao
tic for
you you know very
well how my
evenings be
en
eddy but i hope
you can
put all these
chaos be
hind
us wouldnt be so
sure
about
that
hi thank you
吧 i dont seem to
under
stand why youre
joinin
g us this evening
啊
well to tell you
the tr
uth
哦约
翰你然你说话
呀 lets keep the
discus
sion of the dinner
table
civil shall
we im interested
in wh
at the gentlemman
has t
o say 有人死
肉他要说 HM
哦红酒 would be so
kindto
pass me the red
wine i dont want
to be
the one to have to
ann
ounce the
news but i think
it nee
ds saying someone
was f
ound to have
passed awa
y peacefully in
the stu
dy
area
哎不少
张 so
sorry you
ffun
ok
好 but did you say
someone
yes but its no no
one
that any of
you you
know and its been
dead
with with 小屏
幕那已经定下来
了 was it my
god i think i saw
him
anywell it cant
be you
r
spot i saw him a
moment
ago it wasnt
those
world whoever this
man
was
啊他会觉得
recognizing thats
all why did you
say som
eone in the house
is fo
und dead shortly
after
a complete
stranger turns up
at th
e dog can assure
you
helen ive been
with jo
hn since he
arrived and he has
noth
ing to do with
this and i prefer
it if
you didnt attempt
to
implicate our
guess how did you
get
in i dont
understand w
hat he was doing
here i happen to
have d
iscovered that the
man
we found dead and
the m
an that inviited
me her
e of one in the
mr brupt galley 表
白其实尤其是 have is
roper
gali
哦打雷
了是盘子碎
了 ill
go have a
look
哎
well as i would
say come with
me we need to have
a ta
lk
哦然后就接着七的那部分
了 i need to go and
get
something 然后 tony
去找姐姐
了 the sister ask
for
you 写谢爱丽
丝还有你 please any it
s
fine its under
control
on 就
CTRL i really
ought to
go and find oswald
deal
is going
cold 所以阿迪米和托 ony 到
底什么有什
么关
系 theres nothing
to wo
rry about
annie whats going
on 哼等一
下我们刚刚要做什么来
着
yeah 这之前不认
识但是他们在这这嗯我们刚刚是在挤
啊我刚刚是在切在次之后四到七之
间我不对是在三到七之
间他们又有什么交友安妮和
tony 对啊哦
对我们先弄红酒器九号
嗯身上有红酒刺
刺这是说 helen 寒冷地下的之
后玛莎就是这个
楼玛莎居然是他
吗拆反了
嗯应该是他们后续有交
流
来我们再看一眼
吧随心演员的粉色灯牌刚刚超
离你看到的不是
他对
吧
哦不是
哦我没看
清像零写零一的女生好看安
静你还好
吗我不知道你在说什
么你们俩怎么了
啊
哦好像没有什么嗯线
索妈那人是
谁我之我好像之前见过他安妮安
妮他怎么一下子就知道是在说谁
了应该不可能
吧让我马上立马理解到
了他可能误会
哦
嗯托尼和那个千骨见过面
嗯
哦你见过
吗
哦可能是因为通过用词怎么判断
的
嗯在这之
间托尼和安妮发生了什么事
情很难判断的
呀我们就猜一下
吧在四的时候那个或许他又去了阁
楼
嗯要判断一下安妮和那个托尼
嗯他中间又发生了什
么看来不是不是在鼓楼五
呢哦是在五的时间又见面
了窗户开着外面在下
雨 its me 就是在哪里 go
away cause sing of
trou
ble
ready i have
something
you going to want
to
see 有个东西你一定想看
看 its thats
expensive 都是一眼看起来就
很贵的东
西 fish is going
on havent quite
figure
d it out
yet did you steal
it 能
well
yes look 偷的
stranger ju
st turn
down no one knows
who
is and apparently
hes
looking for
someone cou
ld
rapid 家里日都不
错三猫那
的 i think he came
an of
he left
哦 youre probably
think
ing of
osword
嗯说么是这样
子因为他在哪投
的他在那个老人身上
呢 everyone
else swiss ing 没一个
人承
认他说的承认
了 are you strange
exactly except i
seen t
he name once
before on a small
box t
hat my mom keeps
in a
ring she showed it
to m
e just before i
came
up and met
you but dont
think any
thing of
it see you stoyou
my
妈
哦这是怀
表
yes the stranger
must b
e looking for
it and i dont
want my
mom to be caught
up in
this if things go
wrong why would
things
go
wrong have you
spoken t
o your mom about
this give me be 看起
来 unh
want dont tell
you if
ones looking for
it and ill keep
it aad
ad until we
leait she doesnt
need
to
know i dont be
valuable i dont
know y
ou
it one 缺
钱 i dont really
know a
nyone
else
tony youre go get
far give me the
pockewatch and i
ll giv
e it that you HHDD
know
no
way im give it
this to
you give it to me
or go
know how you stop
it i dont know to
tell
you you dont know
together you dont
know
how much HH 什么
know an
yone out
个 i dont you you
you I
I you can to
it
啊等一
下那四的时
候托尼没
来他一个人在这儿
吗他会自言自语
吗没有没有设置这样的剧情
啊怀表
哦那我们确实猜对
了这是托尼觉得气质比较相像的那个征兵
宣传
单
嗯然后就只剩玛
莎只剩玛莎和那个安妮
了他确实气质要更相像一点
吧
嗯这里还有三个东
西所以他秃
的刚才其他所有人都在客
厅可没有个人承认自己认
识这个时候确实是刚才那没问题的那这么
说我之前在客厅的时
候身在客厅的时
候
呃托尼走
了小维
海海伦海伦和那个艾迪去了一个房
间 tony 单独去了一个房
间小维不知道去哪
了在四的时候小维不知道在哪
里
对然后托尼是偷
的但是他是在这之后偷
的然后捂的时候跑到格美罗高楼去
了他是在四的时候去偷的东
西谢
谢给我差不多一点的粉三灯
牌那托尼在四的时
候从谁的身上偷的东西
呢四的时候他先去了书房
吗但是书房已经发现了那个了
呀书房已经发现了尸体
了但是他觉得这个东西他是在那这之前找
的偷的
吗按理来
说四的时候偷怀
表每天一开始是怀疑他偷那个怀
表是从那个在鲁伯特身上偷
的但看样子又不
是然后从海伦的房间弄看看
哦等一下看看地点能不能添
加对他四四个时候去偷的怀
表应该海伦的房间
OK 那我们走托你一个人去
吧
嗯从盒子里面拿的应该还有一个房间
吧我看那个图的样子的
话酒瓶碎裂的时候偷东西去
喽 i call just
leave
here 没啦哦看箱
子确确实还有很多其他人的房
间海伦的房间没有线索
了这边的厨房
嗯谢冰布洛
芬谢谢冰布洛芬的水晶
鞋谢水晶
鞋
嗯他把他葬葬在这里
的哎
呦只是想听一下语
音不想
看就是怀
孕猫头鹰是怀抱
啊受受灵
体猫头鹰可以附身到钟表之
上怀通常都是在怀抱上面白化凋削的形
象
嗯只是我放错地方
了他还在宅子里面这里看不出来有什么线
索
了但是其他的开出来的话有点担
心
嗯也行
吧如果有海伦的房间的
话肯定有那个芭莎的房
间谢七人张金星的送花花
嗯八莎的房间看起来不适合很
大艾迪的房间也有
了玛莎的房间也有
了海伦的房间有了衣
服应该没有自己的房间啊嗯觉得衣服没有
自己的房
间安妮在国楼托尼呢不须
OK 有偷尼的房间
哦有聪你的房
间还有哪些人
啊还有哦叫什么来
着奥斯
嗯不用出的挺大
呀奥斯房间安妮托尼有了玛
莎有了艾
迪有了维多利亚达米安的房间
吗还是维多利亚的房间
呢大米
OK 那我已
读不
是居然是维多利亚的房间
了
OK 那我们就已经弄完
了房间已经拆完
了应该房间满了大
米从前是
的大米没
有从前写梨雪梨
的你说好
看维多利亚先看一下
啊维多利亚带着安妮过
来维多利亚他妈应该就是那个轮椅太
太为什么维多利亚会到这个聚会里面来
呢米汀没有太明
白因为达米安看起来是跟着维多利亚过来
的但是维多利亚和这一家有什么关系
啊和加利这一家没办法确
定他们没想到我会
来他妈妈是男主人的丈母
娘你记错了
吧乐色衣服和他弟弟
啊艾迪的前女友哼
吐不是
吧他忘不了
他但是说的肯定不是小维
吧应该那虽然也有可能
啊但是感觉应该不会出现那种这种都要订
婚了的情
况还把前女友留在家
里前女友还把妹妹带过来
分并且带着自己的现男友这种事情
嘛服了
吧伊芙说
过维多利亚羡慕
他应该是他羡慕维多利亚的衣
服在厨房的时候说
的这里的时
候对
啊是你际关系应该没这么浅
哦应该是在这个的时候
吗的香度谁谁死
了什么谁死
了是谁谁死了哈哈
哈你谁真都不认
识还然后再回去的小维跟我说过你的
事那哦对小维说那个说很有魅
力嗯
嗯早些时候那或说不定是在一的时
候
对一的时候在厨房吵架
吧看看你们炒了什么艾迪和
天所以他在厨房
哦不是在厨
房是在餐
厅是在餐厅
吗那个房间是哪个房
间台球
室所以他在那儿找戒
指
嗯 you actually
listen t
o me for one
开就是的时
候 i looking
looking war
d to
tonight i
thought
perhaps since my
whole
II
ght youd actually
make
an effort to
pretend y
ou cared about you
in f
ront of the people
for
one
oh im so
sorry you should
have t
old
me was your
birthday
too i
you 那今天本来是谁的声音
啊
呃生啊
darling im
sorry 等一笙歌壁有人在
living 弹
钢
琴
what so you can
make an
other joke about
me and
iignore me the
rest re
st the evening II
not i
gnoring you
eve but we do have
othe
r
guests you think i
want
to be talking your
dow
ned therall living
abou
t his miserable
life i an hetold
ld he
s join the army
for
fun i
mean i leave tony
out o
f
this you
know hes had
problems and you
know thats not
why ang
ry with
you 受过创伤
eve im
sorry tell me what
ive
done
oh come
on if
go easy on the
whisky
why so i can look
more
dignified in front
of y
our
guests were all
trying
to have a pleasant
time 边喝边吵
啊
pleasant i told
you i d
ont wanna talk
think y
ou look at 还卡
believe y
ou
bring 还真是
带还有点小围
观 back to my own
house we supposed
to be
engaged 艾
迪还真是前女友
啊 you still have
feeling but never
enoug
h with you
visit i give you a
ring and what it
does i
s make you more
jealous
than you were
before i dont
know why
even fry 还
可我绝对是还带了妹妹过来 a
thats n
ot what i meant if
啊再买
吃 where did it
go you kill
me 他说了他丈母娘
吧 ok 啊
啊是
的而且他担心的是戒
指他担心会被丈母娘
凶好像怕的是丈母
娘而不是怕他伤心之类的那
种是你一天
哦这是偷你去
找然后来我们继续往后推
吧感觉在厨房这儿应该没有什
么远处传来酒瓶碎裂
声酒瓶碎裂声是一个标记点
啊对
的但是酒瓶到底是在哪序列的
呢远处传来书房
哦这里是在书房摔摔破
的看到尸体的时候摔破
的我们先往后面看
吧偷的他在厨房和 ID 说
话吃后我们迟
到
哦
安你正在试图干
嘛他是不是因为有创
伤一直在那个瞎考
虑安妮又想干
嘛又想干嘛
呀进入此
处
哎他们是一开始就知道厨房什么情况
吗好怪
啊食品储藏室的钥匙应该是为我们准备晚
餐的
人不是艾
迪应该不至于不认识
了那个伤顿
啊奇怪对
的好像没有那个发现尸体的部
分因为一开始在餐厅餐厅一下子就过来变
成这个
了那看来在六的时
候说不定厨房就又发生了什
么至少有他们三个
人在六的时
候至少有艾迪和俊
仔然后相对的不对
呀为什么他们看到那个尸体一点都不惊讶
呀就直接直接说的
是直接说的
是我不擅长处理这种事
情帮我把他挪到外面
去是一共十一共十
天这里一共就是十一个
人
啊对
啊惊讶过
了那说明这里的扒的时候已经不是他们第
一次发现这
个尸体了
呀那难道六的时候也是只有他们两个人尸
体没有出
现那吃肯定不是方
顿也不是传菜有东西送上
来
嗯没办法确认
哦看一下传次某物到达端下盘
子盘子放上
来没有人有什么反
应都是吃的
哦那我们猜测一
下当时六的时候或者七的时候
吧七的时候只有相当一个人在厨
房这个应该不会有问
题这把食物刮到餐盘
上
嗯确实在传菜传菜
井传菜锦这个东西米青只在那个什么这个
杀手不太冷
里面看到
过就其他家看到类似的都是那种传垃圾
的从几楼全能丢到一楼
去那种好稳妥抽这么多线索
吗
嗯所以你到底 i never 啊啊试
试
看还是有自言自语
的打雷的手重物落地的闷想和餐具岁月神
它倒了
吗打雷
打怎么把它劈死
了不是他不是在室内
吗什么东西短路了
吗还是伴随着哪一
声有人开枪
了 bloody
hell what a
meh i bbn n not
great w
ith what
hell 他一开始感慨了
的 itll be move it
outs
ide 刚刚好是雷声
啊经典的就是用雷声那个掩盖墙
体 like its never
reall
y concerned
me i think mother
d dee
s 也不至于从小养到大的管
家他的这完全不认识
吧 listen to
me you dont
explain wh
at youre doing it
who
this roopt
gallleies an
d why weve just
found
a second
body i swear
right 抽值
everything as far
as i
know ive been
invited
in for so unknown
reaso
n by a
moment 来
吧我们去直接去看一眼于室
外发现他是被拖出去
了但是没有讲死
因指甲的指指甲
缝里面有蔬菜的痕
迹人声这么突
然谁能理由
送反正确实是有枪击
了不过现在还没有到那个时
候然后这个是衣
服我离开此
处那这里接下来呢嗯要藏起
来那衣服会衣服会只继续躲在这个房间里
呢我们看看他会继续躲在艾 d 的房间
里面
吗他没有在 ID 的房
间那他会藏在哪里去
呢我没办法判断
了谢谢憨的圆小梦的粉山灯
牌
嗯那难道是艾迪有回房间
喽拿着可可
哦还真是他专门调弄可口
呢 ah i thought i
might
find you
here please the
dolinyo
u II had there bad
peop
le walking
around i brought
you so
me hot
coca
thanks
ki i do are
engaged nex
t
you we are
engagge dont we h
good im terribly
sorry
about earlier
me
too dont be too
innova
te it
yourself
it its not
well im
sorry all the
same
anyway how are you
goin
g to
drink some it
tastes
good but i had
some
earlier in
fact it tastes
exactly
how thondona
always mak
es it for
me are you sure
you did
nt just take it
from t
he put on the
store tha
t was already
there 不认
真 did you know the
pudlua i know
him
eddy its still
pulling
about doesnt
matter re
expose 今天不再放这
里
oh II heard about
that no no
no 我不是指那个 i meant
i fou
nd this
ring dont you
think it
looks
pretty oh
啊是
吧真不认识又想想
我 are you
ID weve already
got on
e wedding to get
through who would
you s
harlling just give
it
back you stop
fooling a
bout so much what
s
going tting 际
忆 i think i fall
en in
love 你辛苦啊
whever it is shes
a lu
cky
girl eddy
啊好怪
呀 you
know i love you
more th
an anything else
in the
whole entire
world
eve thats very
sweet o
f you
ei you not say bad
yourself id climb
the
highest
mountain if i knew
that
when i climb that
moun
tain ID find you 艾
迪嘿
嘿太累了
啊 oh
god 我这个雷声到底咋
了好是
吧 what 妈呀啊
啊我手衣服完全没反应
了为什么衣服完全没反应
了某人挣扎着倒在地板
上是喝那个可可那个可可有什么东西
吗还是说
哦那那那就是衣服那个刚好那个雷声响起
的时
候衣服倒在地上喝
了可可会被雷劈
死你那等一下他的死
粉他的死嘴嘴部周围有可可饮料的痕
迹没有讲死因啊呃这个有有可能不一
样因为你看他在那个走的时
候他把他让那个
谁他让那个约翰先走
了
谢但是谢谢我的小花
花然后艾迪去那个调那个调了过那个可
可然后上楼
了桑顿下毒
了自己写什么不是
吧桑顿没有下图
吧不会
吧还在准备菜
呢也不算知
足他好像就是打算把那个可可带上
去但是不知道他有没有对可可干
嘛仆人为什么要弄涂可可
呢然后仆人为什么又靠自己喝独可可
呢不太确定
啊嗯嗯其他人离开之后才去用餐
的我觉得你现在就能去找他谈
谈那应该就是在那个久的时
候酒的时
候约翰和那个什么在餐厅可能试试看
啊有的时候约翰和奥斯的餐厅
嗯 excuse
me
嗯他看起来看起来不支
持
嗯不知其
名
sorry but i had
rather
enough disturbance
already this
evening i prefer
to be
left eat my
million pie
ce of couri IAAA
key
earlier the key to
the
chaple
l very kind of
you what was
it you y key to
HII hav
e a rupt gali
roopt
t 是不是不认识 y
gpper i had a
great unc
le called ropet
rupet 他他判断人他不是看两点来
判断
的他是靠身上的东
西 in my
TI
though this house
has b
een known to still
hold
the memories of
people
from the
past why do you
ask
啊喂喂
喂 theres been two
debt
sea this
evening one of
them was
a man called rup t
galley
oh so i believe
thats
a these
interesting
是 could you show
me to
九九
九 i went back that
earl
ier
infectant it would
be
moved and the
other one
we found him
downstays
just a moment
ago i think you
was the
butler although
edit di
dnt seem to
recognize
him we used to
have abo
ut many years ago
calle
d george
forms does that
name me
an anything to
you
no i just arrived
earlier im not
connect
ed to this
house if you are
here then its by
no
accident
everything hap
pens for a
reason you may be
try t
o do this house in
a wa
y that you dont
yet
rely if you dont
mind i i was
hoping you
might be able to
expla
in why you
yourself
fa
yeah i wish
invited
ok we doesnt seem
like
im very bold
huc but haas are
alive that reminds
me you were the
only on
e not there when
the re
st of was having
dinner
joon 他不认识还正常
吗因为一开始他也没有自我介绍
啊如果 someone turn
into a
bedroom 只是直接去接他
了我把他接进来
了知道是这一家的仆
人 and i found a
note th
ere about a
performance
of divorce
huma although i
never h
eard the
pianist although
II hav
e the feeling that
some
one in these
houses hid
ing in something h
确实 s
hould just just AA
inincience i
happen to
know the
important i want
to go
and have a looking
tony
room ask him to
you wh
ats in his
bedside
draw 让他给你看看他的床头柜蜜有
什
么难道 i 他当时是看到
了 im sorry for
interru
ption
you this
conconsation h
as been more
informativ
e for me that it
has fo
r
you im sure
啊我们先把明确的线索直接继续看下去
吧蛇托尼的房间是约翰一个人过去的
对应该是他之前什么时候去了偷这个房
间
嗯他不是一个人过去
的难道托尼也
在
嗯托尼确实
hello i dont
think we
ve properly met
you
here
哼 please come on
in i want to talk
to
you
great that makes
two of
us as
in i also want to
talk
to
you
对为什么跑给我去
啊 i havent seen a
pock
et
watch 对啊
啊就灵卡 f 他真的很像那种北海妄想
mom so if youre
lookin
g for it dying all
the
rost im not
looking fo
r
it you must come
to thi
s house looking
for
something i dont
belie
ve a second that
youd
come 他没有弄
丢他让那个他们帮他
抢他让他
切 the only place i
ve s
een that name
before is
on a box that
containe
d a pocket
watch i know that
watch
is missing a see
嘘
有 how do i fit it
this you still
啊
what why would he
invit
e me to to three
this
more 但是为什么要邀请我来这里偷
看
呢 either wasnt
real or
some deceased
relative and that
perha
ps you would forge
the
invitation
yourself to
have an excuse to
steal
his
thing 干嘛偷的不怎么
样专门再来一
趟 i understand
that you
sususpiciof
of given that i
dont e
xactly fit in
me i long as to
find a
way to prove our
minison i its
confused
as you are us to
what
s happening
it but im far
easier i
f we work together
on w
ho not
confuse i see you
re tr
ying to hoddwag
the oon
est of this
house i you meking
work
ge as long as you
leav
e me out of
it
heh stop
h ah
ha whats
that im just just
mind
ing of this
see how did you
know th
at was
there im just a
second
ago you were
trying to
put a blame on
me
wow touch
it im not trying
to bl
ame
you i told
you i dont care
what i
t is your up
to i just minding
ding
this business and
looki
ng out for
myself 是 two
people of
the idea this
evening a
nd youve been
keeping a
gun in your jraw
too
喂 with someone
short
no i didnt say
that
不 its suspicious
all t
he same
哈 give
up i clearly dont
have
anything to do
with
it i hardly know
anyone
else
here would neither
do i
how great theybe
both
in the same
boatat now please
get o
ut of my
room
哦钢琴
声 the piano
啊 i know to see
earlier but i don
t thi
nk i need to go
and
see 他是什么时候看到枪的
呢看一下
啊他在餐厅之前在艾迪的房
间难道在八的时候那个奥斯看到他房间的
什么东西
了他说在七的时
候这外面看到的之类的看不
到前面有个钢琴
蛇前面在一开始他们吵架的时
候有攻琴
手七的时
候因为每天在小七的时
候是不是他去拿
喽枪用的时候有看到
吗是
的前面一直都不知道他在哪里
他但是总有一个时间
点他是看他是知道托尼的房间有什么东西
的没有
上一开始他跟安妮讲话了之
后他跟安妮讲完
话然后哦四的时候去厨房
了人五的时候去托尼的房间了
吗看一下
啊是他要想去那个流世
组
嗯四岁还在五的时
候我开始就没有五六七
都不知道他在哪五六
七他都有可能跑去那个什么的房间
呢 tony 也在托尼五的时
候不在托
尼五的时候在阁
楼那难道是六的时候跟托尼一起在他的房
间五
六如果托尼也在的
话只能站了 ok 六的时
候
嗯这三抽屉他是每个人的房间都去搜
了不一
定 will you go
through m
y
things
no
no not at
all i was just
having a
look
around i didnt
realize
this room as
occupy
right its
osworld is it
osword
galli i dont
believe w
eve
哦所以他知道他是个小胡
子 what youyou
doing in
my
room
well that when i
was
younger this used
to be
on nurse
rates not your
nursery
any
longer
easy dont come in
again this is you
norma
lly treat at new
acquaintance 别 don
t te
st my patient
嗯 get out of my
room theres no
need to
be
suspicious
boy im leaving 嗯
gy 确认
嗯确认了什么东
西然后又拉回去
了把枪挪到更里面一点了
吗难道不啊血瓶布洛芬此并不能奋
斗至臻原皮花式夸
夸谢
谢你的至臻原皮花式夸
谢确实也知道他应该是叫家
啊很可爱而已
哈家里
有谢谢夸
夸那我们计算时间
线往后走好像想不出来有什么嗯想不出来
有什么线
索但总感觉这个奥什么他应该搜了不止一
个人的房
间虽然我们也可以在那个推断一
下六的时
候在这七的时候就去呃七的时
候他应该是在自己的房间里面我看一
下但是他会在自己的房间里面自言自
语
嗯也有可能是在找钥
匙那看来不止他一个
人他不在自己的房间里
边大家在吃饭的时
候他在哪
呢他不会去嗯托尼的房间已经去过
了玛啥
呀他不会去搜那个了
吧身怀矫持那个了
吧餐厅的对话是不是好像跟约翰说
了看一眼
哦等一下看一
下曾经的时
候他有说是
吗刚刚在楼下哦藏书室的那个房
间然后被仓促改成了卧
室地板有点
粘那晚餐的时候还在那发生了一家一张便
条写着关于什么下课幽默幽默曲的节目
单但是没有听说过那个谁的房
间里面会有钢琴的东西
呢
对还是某个卧室里
面托尼的已经确定不吃
了那就是海南呢或者维多利亚的感
觉维多利亚的戏份太
少那维多利亚是弹钢琴
的
嗯艾迪的从今已经排除了海
伦玛
莎
嗯还有一个房
间我们没有排出来
吗地点我们都已经听完
了不是书房
吗
哦书房被改成了一个卧
室倒是也符合符合这个条
件就是
了看一
点他们是临时改了一
个
嗯但是我临时改成了一个卧
室罗当时是不是也说到过那个地
方有个什么钢琴谱的
呀
嗯哼哼哼哼哼哼
嗯哼
嗯哼哼宝宝宝宝宝宝扑通砰
砰嗯
嗯嗯 good
heavens 就是那个死的时
候管家死掉的时候啊就没
了我的老天啊是嗯
来然后这边是个托尼钢琴
曲会是在谁的房间
呢是
的至少七呃至少在这个时间所有人都在
嗯难道真的是个意
外管家的死是个意
外至少我在我们的视角看来他们确实都有
不在场证证
明
了对
啊就看一下那个维多利亚回豆
料有微弱的薰衣草香
气想去维多利亚的房间看
看看看维多利亚他什么时候有可能会在自
己房间二三
四五
六都不知道在
哪哎
呀但是也不能这样穷举
啊嗯拿到钥匙
嗯这个已经拿到了是
吧那十的时
候他会不会已经去教堂了
呢看一下拿到
胶你拿到钥
匙他应该会往这边走
的没有过
去他会和谁一起
呢
哦我们不知道不是
九
嗯不是十的
话难道是十
一或者说他不止一个人过
去那可能他不止一个
人不止一个人的
话还会有谁
呢人数有点太多了
呀喜欢看看注钢琴
哦再往前面的
话我们之前不知道客厅的这一
场最后就是不知道维多利亚去哪
了那如果四维多利亚没有去其他地方的
话可能他就回房间了
哦快到家回房
间他没有在房
间我都
要你不要到处乱走
啊等一下是四
吗
对四的时候不知道维多利亚在
哪想知道到底是哪个房间里面有钢琴
啊四手安妮知道
呀新
说安妮在他的那在阁楼里面
吧应该可以试试看
了安妮应该是一个人在阁楼或者安妮和维
多利亚在阁
楼见
到
哦那 tony 走了之
后那个奥什么来之
前他还跟他还跟维多利亚见了一面
哦去找他妹妹了也对他当时说妹妹可能干
嘛
了 sorsearch 也不是居然当
他当时看到
可可能就去
了 it wouldnt
happen
again any i need
to tal
k to you about
somethin
g you
write 谢
谢
they you know
where it
s just
stream
对当时在门口的时
候不是说有东西下来
吗
啊一命
啊 with
eddy i dont know
why h
e 不知道他为什么邀请我回回
invi tho
ught we be friends
now hes we
eat 原来你也不知道 what
did he
say 快一
点 but its not
like he
said anything
really we just
seemed a
ngry with me for
some
reason what can
why we
hear you dont
need to
be friends of
them i know what
what w
ould
you 你把东西给他没
啊 i can find
somewhere
to hide it if that
s wh
at you
mean 然后 because j
这个人不
下 but its not
that bad
is
it i was hoping he
d no
tice
combent i thought
it mi
ght be a nice
gesture 把这 i think
it w
as a mystery
ah i ininted you
around
to show up his new
engagement you
know so dont feel
like
you owe him
anything 哈
for thats rich
coming
from
you please
big you can tell
mandy you
darling you can
stay wi
th us as long as
you
like but i
know but see you
to her
at some
point what this
wont o
r this until
eddies not
worthy were
time but serious
sy i for
god sajust stay
out of
trouble
well you i was
already but i
know but see you
later darling 露台锁门
了
吗
哦上门
了不知道安妮做什么时候才好像是瞒着妈
妈
的
哎还以为是种善意的表
示然后结果对方没有发
现然后他就让他妹妹帮他保管一
下这是拖不过去
狼
嗯或许能够知道安妮的画
像难道是苦哀
酒苦爱酒有什么那个
吗古埃酒有什么寓意
吗善意的提
醒那玛莎的话应该就是一首
歌至少现在行形象起
了
对而且是附近的村庄发现
的不会还有村庄
吧附近或者村庄 CSORYURT 的
有三灯牌没
有村长应该不会出现
了然后然后这里走了之后落锁
了然后又来阁楼
了然后这里呢六的时
候安妮安妮在格斗干嘛
呢
哦六六六尝试进进
错同一个代码两
次不好意
思这个手感不过大家是不是也看不
到下面我们来退出一下
啊退出一
下明天处理好像卡了个
bug 下面有一点点看不清谁不幸重名
的六六
六谢谢你的六六
六好
的嗯
嗯咕咚现在看着应该是正常的那继续
吧我们现在到我过十二
点谢
谢
CHR 我飞
手谢
CHR 我飞秀的舰
长谢谢你去岁舰
长
哎丫
头 thank
you 谢谢你续费的舰
长感谢谢谢谢
谢然后谢林英谢林音的五杀任务六星光铃
铛谢灰色的
幺二四的粉钻灯
牌谢狂拉丽迦现在的粉钻灯
牌谢
谢我们在这里看
看如果托尼在这个地方没有离开的
话十一他会还在这个房间
吗坏了托尼会待在自己的房间
吗是
的没有待在自己的房
间有可能没有拍下
来哎
呀要猜就到底去了哪一个地
方但是呢不管在哪个地
方弹钢琴
的肯定不止一个人奶
油有谁有谁感觉会弹钢琴
呢狐狸钢琴钥匙这感觉是死掉
的那个人是的两次钢琴声来推测一下
啊首先在吵吵架的时
候一开始吵架的时候是有人
调
哎但是没办法判断
了因为后来的人出现都是在吵架之后
了能够确认的就是弹钢琴
的弹钢琴
的不是就不是桑
顿不是艾
迪也不是那个也不是伊
芙其他人都有可
能背景里面能找得到钢琴
吗
嗯什么叫背景里面能找得到钢琴
吗对
了主要是想知道钢琴是在哪个房间这样来
排除
吗这个房间没有这个房
间没有这房间没有车
房前面有维多利亚的房间不知道长什么
样龙口牛这里好像也没有折留声机和台
球偷那个房间里没有阁楼也没
有那所以要不然在奥什么的房
间要不然在维多利亚的房
间但是倒是有那个奥什么他在那儿说那个
琴谱的事
情不知道和这个有没有关系
啊看一
下
嗯虽然我从没听说过那位钢琴
家但是他注意到了这个一般不弹钢琴的人
可能不会注
意这
个谢
谢雨雨
落青青的粉色灯
牌客厅图片的右边客厅图片的右比
奥还的还真是客厅有钢
琴那看一下
吧但是你你不知道在那里会遇到谁
呢谢一一发爆炸舰的人气
票谢萧离夜路的粉色灯
牌假设是二五会弹钢琴
哦不是我们漏掉了什么线索
吗目前的嗯看一
下谢
谢三 q 在 SK 的粉三灯盘
嗯安之前的
事真对不
起你还好
吗我不知道你在说什
么这个是在说揪娃娃的那个事情
吗约翰托尼适合达米安一起过来
的六的时候托尼和达
莲
哎但是可能只是刚刚
好乌兰约好安
妮我海伦一起
过哪里是
了一直都在阁楼
的安零六的时候才要沟楼
吗应该是安妮海螺和约翰安妮海伦和约翰
从阁楼
吗
啊哼肉的时
候等一下
啊先看一下他有没有不在场证
明六的时
候约翰在那个书
房那安妮和海伦 ok 两个两个人不
在那也不对
啊难道在海伦的房间不是看一下
啊六的时候还以为他一直都
在还以为他一直都在弄阁楼
呢或者说其他人都是进来的那就看六的时
候有谁已经
到了约翰安妮海
伦托尼达米安那六的时
候已经有人在餐厅
了反过来推的话嗯正不在达米安和衣服在
其他房
间然后这两个哎呀记不住状态位置哦哦还
挺方便
的这里是所有人的状态都知道
了然后这里的
话其实安妮这个时候应该是和谁在哪儿有
见面
的哈里玛莎海龙写帕特开拓的粉丝安登
牌
嗯然后安妮和海伦是后面进来的
话五六九有可能哦不是 etty 五六
七五六
七可能已经早就在餐厅
了看一下
啊这里艾迪是什么时候进来
的埃迪是中途进来的
吗还是一开始就在托尼谭米安那
ID 不是哎
呀起名字好麻烦
哦约翰安尼海
伦托尼达米安还能偷你的比较
闹那就是五六七五六七都是一开始就在餐
厅
的在六的时
候他们都在餐厅
吗
对安利和海螺应该是在一块呃一块
的没有这
受主要是吃过推
断主要是这个推断不一定有
效他们嗯他们也不一定是一直待在客
厅直播更早一批
来
哦没选餐厅
吗意外了
哦确实是他们三
个现在这
儿
hello
mom its
哦打电
话但是
yes 挂
了 you were just a
littl
e early for
dinner thats all
玛莎本来想
打电
话但是但是发现了书房的事
吧 luits notice
organiz
ing dinner for a
house
full of people
with out
only one member of
stuff i am
sorry mom
said but it was my
faul
t
for i hope that
you don
t mind that i
brought
that manning from
the c
old
mum i thought you
look
very
harmless are we
talking
about mister
hobs hes the list
of m
y
concerns its nice
to h
ave some new
company if
you ask
me and its a
pleasure
to have any here
here a
s well
victoria so i
wouldnt
worry
嗯 is theres
something
else to be
concerned
about
嗯那 no
heavens no look at
the
two of you at
you gender
again you make a
great
pair
哦
对他说的想报警来
着 eddy was just
complai
ning about how he
could
nt find
something when i
walked
in he was just
talking
about old
times 巧克饭 was
looking f
or some chalk for
the c
ues youtube was so
clos
eas
children its so
funny
seeing the
both if you hear
again you
know
victoria i really
think
well never
mind
no can we please
not ta
lk about us as
children
oh he was so
gmpmpy you
were
little i remember
they
used to have that
bracelet she made
you
eded do you make
ones f
or each
other i
three the way is 有
啊在他身上
啊 if you wanted me
to m
ake you another
one what you have
to do
with
ask i thought we
were s
upposed to be
having di
nner
mom 嗯
嗯 why dont you
both ta
ke a
seat i am sure it
will
be ready
soon 他和 ID 和那个小维是一
起进来的
呀那这么说的
话那我的时候他们两个在什么地方
呢艾底和小
薇当时小维是去了一趟阁
楼然后二和九在一起二和九没有在鼓楼六
岁阁楼的
话在海伦的房间
吗当时我们是不是试过了六的时
候没在海伦的房
间在阁
楼没在餐
厅他们能在书房
吗在台球室
哦我的时候在台球室
哦
对找找巧克粉的时
候那我先把它那个弄了
吧不
的
嗯但是戒指也是找到了
的是鸡子鱼肉粉三的
牌
呃 eddy hi
victoria have you
lost
something eves
ring
啊我这里不是说说了才想
切 would you like
me help you look
for
it you could
do
thanks i am sorry
about
earlia i went to
go and
talk to any just
now and she
woulccause
any more
trouble 但其实不是他做的
事 and im sorry
frenrur
upting
you i shouldnt
have ha
ve let that man in
honestly
vik its
fine im
sorry if i seem to
be i
n a bad
mood its a 我都不知道是
is e
verything right
with
you
indeed though it
ll sor
t itself
out we just had a
bit o
f an
argument say
sure um these
things
happen ive been
meanin
g to
say 上次见
面 i should we left
thin
gs on a sour
note the last time
we
met and im sorry
that
we dont
talk so often
these
days but ive been
busy
with
damy and its
girl its
fine it was my
faut
t shouldnt II
stupid t
o think
well that i was a
long
time
ago II still want
this
to be
friends of
course its nice
to hav
e you here 加上青梅竹马这
这一层关
系 but 是叫前女友过来就显得没有
那么奇怪
了就是 II poorted it
as so
on as i get 到戒指了
that c
ome
on lets go to
dinner 你不是海伦河奥不会
被然后海伦和安妮这里的时
候那个奥什么是来托尼的房
间
哎好难猜
啊他们到底在做什
么这些人当时都在客厅
吗难说一的时候安妮应该就已经在阁楼了
吧来安妮阁楼检
查是
的太太可了哈哈
哦把窗子打开了
哦有人敲门
哦啥什么都没
有只是给了他一个在场证
明是
的他出生点在这里来继续在这儿看看
吧所有人都
哦但八的时候
呃八的时候剩下哪些人
啊其他三个人走
了然后八 ID 的房间要看看吧的时
候在餐厅还有哪些人就不在安妮走
了安尼托尼托尼不
在艾迪不
在剩下的这些人都在这里
吗打包
吗没打
爆还有人走
了安妮本身是在这里吃饭
的充值一
下看是谁送
了
嗯维多利亚
哦玛莎去叫人了
吗忘记了这一
歌谢谢 ok
nothing i
swear i just heard
that
name before i
apprecia
te the honesty
earlier too many
people
nowadays seem to
favor
pollighess over
giving
a straight
mwer thats quite
all
right miss
doour do you know
anyth
ing about what
happen she saw
someone
steal something
from my
bedroom is that
right
day
yes i dont know
think
whats been stolen
a po
cket watch of
mine what i dont
if i
m so
sorry if i
accidentally
let a thief into i
hou
se out
goh i dont think
this
is related
II check the dead
man
myself theres no
reaso
n to think his
death wa
s
suspicious im
sure the
res a simple
explanati
on behind why he
was
here could i ask
you to
keep an eye out
for my
watch it would mea
a lo
t me if you could
return i think the
two
of us a
raststout thats
quite
all
right misses
doour
嗯 i think i might
know
who to talk to 爱
你 would you like
to hav
e a word with me
in bix
ks
room you know what
its
fine ill going
took
tianian its not
like i
done in
me
ok 这里有新的呃
呃 but you too be
nice t
o each other
then but ill go
and ch
eck that
everythings t
o
upstand if there
is som
ething going on
sweet a
rt that i wont be
goin
g
long we
finisyou
oh go and play the
pian
o in the living
room how did that
sound i listen out
for
it 那我们先看维多利亚那边
吧他去餐厅楼上
了爱你 come with
me 哎
呦要单独谈
话
对钢琴先手来
了那酒的时候看先看一下
啊这是餐厅厨房海伦的房
间餐厅楼上玛莎的房
间那就是玛莎的房
间维多利亚一个人过去了久的是他和马上
一起过去的
吗那确实也有可能不是阵容
上就是他们马上一起过
去都克
兰
嗯哼麻烦
嗯 how are
you
right im
fine thank
you just give me a
mome
nt to
recover and ill
be bac
k downstairs in a
second why are
you you things on
the
soul did something
happ
en
it its time
really i dont
think an
ythings broken at
leas
t come on come and
sit
down or pick it
all up
later im
sorry
victoria but dont
worr
y
math if its be a
hard
evening for you to
manmanit then you
shoul
d know that youre
doin
g incredibly
well theres no
way i y
ou be you a
celebring t
o see me very kind
of y
ou to
say i really
wanted thi
s evening to be a
celebration but
what wi
th strangers
coming int
o the house and a
dead
body turning
up i no longer
feeling
control of my own
house if it helps
to he
ar
it
oh think youre
taking
this far better
than so
me of the other
guests
honestly
math i dont know
how y
ou
days so
calm h honstly 是什么
东西上来的
吗 you might be
stranger
s to be celebrit
of my
own
house chinese is
runnin
g a large and
bringing
up a sun on my own
for
so many
years but 所以 now
it sti
ll feels as if i
have n
o idea what im
doing do you mind
if i
ask why do you
always w
ear a
ring what i
suppose i n
ever noticed when
i was
younger i dont no
不
还 sigh thought i
seem
stronger if people
thou
ght i had a man in
my l
ife at ive
reached an
age now where im
quite
content as i
am 那他就把戒指取下来
了我放到抽屉里去
了 you look better
witho
ut
it i am sure it is
only
way you
down i wanted to
tell y
ou something
early er victoria
when
the three of us
are in
the dining room
just be
fore
dinner whats
that i just i didn
t wa
nt to say it in
front o
f
eddy but its been
wond
erful to meet
damian
today im really
glad t
he two of you seem
to b
e so happy
together i think
youd
make a wonderful
husband if you
think 看了
下一
段他打电话之
后麻烦 im glad you
like
him i think he
wasnt t
oo keen on coming
here
this
evening but how do
you
have pein enjoying
himself
now
victoria im glad
that
you an idea still
frien
ds you were so
close wh
en you were
children its been
nice
to see him
again
it can i ask out
of
interest do you
know if
heis romantic
councita
ble with anyone at
the
moment but i dont
want
to ask him
myself 哎
嗯
no that im aware
he li
kes to keep
himself to
himself 坏
了对对
对 i wish him in
the
best i know that
whoeve
r he ends up with
这家人 w
ho make her very
happy
until thanks for
cheeri
ng me up
victoria 所以 are
you
welcome
哎所以小维在这个时候还不知
道可就拆来他的闹力太羡慕
的 i just need a
minute
to
collect 但是他后来不是知道
吗
哎那个还说
哎不是那个管
家还说小维
呃是那个管家跟衣芙聊的
吗说小维说他好
话那个是管家编的
吗天哪好
乱然后在这边他去找玛莎
了然后那个打米
啊等一下看一眼达米
安
嗯和安妮去维多利亚的房
间
对丹尼安和安利去维多利亚的房
间家里人太多
了是长
的终
于
annie this doesnt
need
to be a long
discussion just
tell me
you you the pock
on 直接说给我一下
about is that all
you w
anted to did
me im not blaing
you f
or
anything just tell
me w
here it
is what would you
blame i havent
even do
ne anyone to me
any
please dont make
a fus
s out of youre
not
stupid i havent
to me
why ve got
it that ve got
it what ve got
it 然后给他
了 i havent even
been n
ew hellen s II
dont h
ave you
stoit but helhelen
said
you you know you
did i also saw you
and
tony talking
secretivel
y over
dinner and tony
said th
at he going to get
something but
no no t lying to
me
any i didnt have
anyth
ing to do
that how
靠 i
understand just
give me
something to go
on you already
know
everything but the
soun
ds of did tonies
probab
ly hidden it
somewhere thats
all i
needed to hear
啊 im sorry that i
m sl
eeping with your
sister
annie that doesnt
mean
we have to be
enemies 什么 you too
a lu
cky muthd didnt
make y
ou sleep me at
it im sure its
not th
at
bad have you had a
chan
ce to me the
others
yet ive spoken to
tony
that almost landed
me
in
trouble and i came
down
to the living room
jus
t before
dinner but only
hellen
was
there i thought
this pl
ace was going to
be mor
e
lively to be
honest
啊客厅和好 HI cant
stay
drinking sherry
with tw
o older women was
how i
expected my
evening to
go 不是 TUSE
interested 粉
色灯盘 dead bodies on
admi
re their fun that
was
dramatic
ah you dont know
anyth
ing about this
rupet ga
li do
you
no that id expect
to i
no although i did
see t
his
one strange man
walking
about he used to
liver
a long time
ago i think ill
go ask
him try and break
the
news whom
gently if this is
one o
f his
relatives then it
could
那个就是死的那个人
哦
thanks feedwie
sweet
art you always to
came
out to
me kiss
kiss 嗯哎啊不
懂反正七之前六他们两个是在六的时
候他们两个是在客
厅他和海伦还能长什么
样忘了
嗯设营养关系倒是听得出
来就算他不不加那个括
号
hello are
you
tony
mom thats
right
darling do you
come joi
n
me theres a bthe
sherr
y over there from
the
earlier i dont
drink i just came
to
say i think you
are muc
h populy
watches
oh
yeah
stolen i shouldnt
brought it was me
in th
e first
ay 现都还不知道被偷
了别人就来告诉他是谁偷
了 you
mean i havent had
it f
or
long im not sure
why i
bought it really
now w
ith strange men
walking
around the
house you
know i spoke to
one fun
ny gentleman in
here just a moment
to g
o that wanted to
go thi
s mp in the dead
of nig
ht that rather not
attr
act the attention
of me
n like
that tony
said he said there
was
a name on the
box
oh i didnt seem
to
recall 真
上 never mind 卖
点
嗯 you said you
knew of
the whereabouts of
my
watch 接下来不
对 i just meant id
seen
someone 他没打算给直接说
呀 i didnt see who
it
was 哎
呀 thank you for
coming
to tell
me not even my own
daug
hter seems to want
to i
nform me of whats
goin
g on
today 米
亲现在已经有点混
乱
oh im sorry to
hear 只要会弄他们之间的关
系 i think dinner
should
be ready
soon 说起来嗯对他这里其实说
了托尼说上面有个名
字但是我呃但是后面其实也说得通
啊就是托尼跟他聊到
过但是后来他又看到有人拖走
了这种嗯解释倒是也能解释
的通就是嗯然后这里是有雪梨
球
对一开始说的是从你后面后面说的是一这
里呢海螺和
盗尔海伦后面在客厅的
话这里说不定他们也是在客厅见面
的不说
话等会到
啊好
哦他说他碰到那么奇怪的绅
士要去要去教
堂 excuse
me i dont think
weve
met
no i dont think
we hav
e 太能长了 leshould to
meet you
dann sorry
is is something
out
there its too
dock to
see it
properly but the
chapel
sit somewhere out
ther
e on the
hill i would have
like
ked have visited
it 对
的 perhaps 是 i get
the c
hd 什某人小后开发了超变
弹就了别人吃了
的
嗯 forgive
me i am very
distractiv
e the
eeing 而且这种场合很奇
怪想以难以识个有什么玩
戏 i think eve
mentione
d you could you
remind
me how you are
related
to the
family but i am
the las
t of my family
们家族最后一
人 i have no
relation to
our hosts other
than t
hrough the house
itself im sorry
to hea
r
that do you mind
if i a
sk whether youre
married i always
prefer
to live
alknow now that i
think
it it is perhaps
to sh
ame the line of
true
galleys 所以他是正统血
脉 do you have me
you 过
yyself
yes two of
them there are
somewher
e around the
house although i
can ne
ver seem to hold
on to
them as much as i
might
like that is misr
dwa
here 海的是衣服和
tony
no hes a way you
doing
something
else but he said
it wou
ld have like to
have be
en
here
well its been
lovely m
eeting
you
mr dwa 米斯皮尔
的 thank
you
好处理完成
了大家都在的地方都
大大概知道了二的时候应该剩下几个人都
去客厅了
吧除了这个二楼谁谁谁
炖香
炖可能已经到厨房去
了算
了我们也不用现在去排
除然后发的时候
嗯扒的时候
啊为什么桑顿还有一个桑顿还能在厨房
吗他的尸体当时应该是在厨房的相
顿在扒的时候是在厨房已经死掉
了但是这个应该没办
法再那个
呀不会出现了
呀尸体尸体不算了
吧
对那嗯想快了看一下
啊扒的时候他们在这里
聊然后这分成两
批他去了玛莎的房
间维多利亚去了马莎的房
间然后维多利亚应该是单独走了
吧对我我都是他去了客
厅十的时
候他应该在客
厅但是他是一个人在客厅
吗反正他在客厅弹钢
琴谢虚空喵的粉色灯
牌
对十的时候在客厅弹钢琴时
候十一的时
候两个人应该就过去
了
哦那个客厅靠近空调
了但是他听出了他一个人
吗客厅不止他一个
人十的时候客厅还有可能有哪些人
呢太多了
哦他应该还在继续在这儿吃
饭然后艾 d 这两个哦 edi 可能
也跑到客厅
去
了不是很你不是很确定
啊然后这边是维多利亚走
了艾迪会在一起
吗
对约翰去找钢琴
声是在十一的时候找的钢琴
声但是我们要先确定十的时
候在客厅有哪些
人然后才能把约翰他们加
上先看看艾迪有没有到客厅来
啊不吃了十一也许会提到
十他在和谁聊
天那试试看
嘛先看看十一的
话反能达里
安听到了暗号会过
来约
暗听到钢琴声会过
来至少他们相个在
哎那倒计十的时候还有谁
呢 vick is
everything all
right i am ine
sweet ha
d come
here 有可能有人来
了客厅邀请了
II just just king
king
to something one
here 确
实他确实刚刚在这里和别人聊
天 i can and 就是可以弹钢
琴
吗 would you work
about
excuse
me mister hobs
mici i just im
sorry i wont just
wjus
t like to have a
poick
look
ch
piano did you find
that
pocket watch
piato i found
it but its hardly
impo
rtant right
now i was someone
else
嗯 i couldnt tell
it
first i thought
they we
re just aslelewait
什么意
思达米安又发现
了 i dont know it
was a
young
woman it wasnt
nice to
see 还是他不认识谁的衣
服他认识了安安
米他有聊还有谁
啊
you you may be
interest
ed to know that i
ve di
scovered another
body a
s
well 衣
服他已经认识
了他要装不认识
吗
somethingnot
right this doesnt
feel
like an
accident but i don
t un
derstand why
anyone wou
ld do
this 你可不可以婆
人 maybe it wasnt
even
intentional
it 你啥怕什
么 i dont
know i
suppose so i dont
see
any signs of
injuries o
r
struggle
oh
gosh 他是要装不认
识 i dont think it
can
be
that 因为安妮肯定是杀妹
妹没办法 found a gun
in his
bet i
draw i know there
there
haver been any
gunshots but steel
喝热
口可都不是衣
服 think about
this do you think
he ha
s nothing to do
with th
is
sweetheout it
wouldnt
make any
sense i dont
understan
d what motive
anyone wo
uld
have who even were
thes
e
people
well it is been
acting
very 那他可能就是要在他未婚妻面
前或者在他妻子面前要装自己不认
识 who is he
again
啊但是我们确实知道衣服是什么
before m
ah a and
eddy but i was
never al
lowed in a wood
room and i was
younger but
honeely
ly i dont know
what he
s doing back care
tonight if i had
to pic
k someone mad ough
LQQ
扣的超好看
vick we should
leave i dont want
to s
ee how this
ends i know 到另一面
will h
and back the
pocket tor
ch and 去问的对
啊就可以去看看看 student
me a f
ew mthes
away well get any
some
泡 go there
哦 when recommend
that w
ill lane to be
practica
lly flooded by now
and
never where where
else
will be a right
bug looks like we
re st
aying the
night then dont
worry
嗯他认识
识他能想想在己己妻子子前说说不认识之
类的
吧 neither watched
or in
volved in this
anyway nor is amy
for t
hat
matter II hope 的
hear w
hat 切入 to raise
voices 然后你们在台球室吵起来
了朝下圣
地他们说 i can
能 and they someone
else
there too 一
直
hello 我
tony i cant make
it ou
t
properly what did
you
say 李虎还是愿意说 my
children
哈 do you think she
is
哦对
呀 wait vick a
sweet
out come
on everyone else
will h
ave heard it
too
嗯好多人
啊本来就是实在收不着了
啊从哪里开始
呢十的时
候他和一个不置这里的人聊他这样这样的
说
法看起来十的时
候在客厅里面只有他和另外一个
人当我们猜到 ID 好像艾迪是错
的
嗯我们刚刚猜的 IDID 是错
的但是人还有点太多
了要不先做个鼻涕
啊已保存这个我们其实已经知道
了就一个旧的钢琴演奏
单阿里亚韦斯
特这个应该是和那个相关的
啊是十一的时
候海伦和一个男生在吵
架离我的孩子远一
点海伦
呃先块石
吧十的话感觉那个嗯呃达米安发现了那个
尸
体应该是在艾迪的房
间不知道为什么他会到那个房间
去他可能不想回
答为什么他要到那个房间
去还是说已经不要衣服
了还有两个年轻女性
啊没
了此人不算
哦 im sorry to
disturb
you 买
的
对死人不算拿
人 are you
awake id like to
ask a
few questions
madam im looking
for a
pocket
watch if you could
just
tell me whether
you se
en it or
not then ill
leave you
to get
back you
sleep
madam 转
身你就看到他了
哦 god
oh got 他以为他睡着
了先是这个号
码谢沙天夏天扇春风之凉的都不
行弱的不这么冷静
吗还看一下有没有有没有怀表就开始
了就开始舔包
了哦
哦行
吧
嗯揉食的时
候客厅也有人十的时
候客厅我们能确定的是维多利亚
神然后但是呢他说的说我那个语气感觉应
该不是熟悉
的
人十一和十都已经死掉
了 helen helen 是他妈的
不
对海顿是托
尼他
吗 tony 偷你和衣服他
吗他有可能会跟海伦
聊这个感觉是不是按时间顺
序对
呀还真是和海伦先聊
天是想判断他们的熟悉程
度如果是夏令营那边的人的
话
嗯你这他应该会直接
说他说的是这个人 you look
well
啊说明不是很熟悉
啊 you helen
嗯听 moca
said shed
been
嗯 but excuse me
sit dow
n
darling theres no
poin
t ignoring it 啊 of
than
k
you
嗯还就就是 iphone 瑞
凌 i am
sorry i 就是不可以以 it
will
turn
up how are you
feeling oh and
哎 if its
nothing i must
have eat
en some of
things
fine
darling ive been
throu
gh it
with
哦是因为他玩那个
呃那是之前说了是怀孕
了所以一直不舒服是
吧才说的我一眼就看出来
了海
伦 at the second
time so much words
哦 i think ive
only met
one of
yours of
course youve seen
tony
around
no my first time
it did
nt lead to
anything
啊
well it was a
blessing
that it worked out
with
tony at least
哎衣服
吗 i you
哦衣服不是他女儿
吗 nit is
alright 衣服难道是
mino 是脱尼的感
觉还是不是他亲手
呢 does he know im
goin
g to tell him
soon wont wait
back
home ill tell him
hold
on to
him wont
you i found
out i was
expecting
again just after
the wa
r broke
out i had to tell
my hu
sband about it
during t
he brief time he
had of
f from the
front it didnt
feel re
al like we were
pretending i
always bel
ieve that things
would
continue after the
war
reacted like they
would but he didn
t com
e
back 看样子
说 never known his
father im so
sorry i dont know
how
you did
it if i didnt
have
amy i what her
thinking
about i shouldnt
put t
hat in your
head
no no talking you
哦所以他刚刚是想跟达米娅
说 no nice talking
to
you
no the advice i
you 想到讲
了这一部分了之
后所开始弹弹钢琴叫过来
了 victoria
victoria mic
saco
well
darling i hope
everythi
ng goes
well 看样子可能是
吧不舒
服再加上听完这个了之
后他本来想想借这个开话口的
吗快点想算
了没关
系他说
没我没
事后来我只是想见你一张还没有打算
讲
嗯看样子这个时候还没有打算
讲只是起了一下念
头然后是
no 那我们选十一还是选十二
啊海伦海龙和谁在台球社离
果我的孩子远一点吃过
吗海螺回
家我是从 a
到然后另外几个人一起再过去
了毕竟离我的孩子远一点
了艾
迪欢迎
ATA 别再废我
了 they should be
around
somewhere if you
go wawait 刚刚从客厅过
来 ill be there
later i
just i need to saw
some
thing
out ive hardly
seen an
yone all
day you
know if theres
somethi
ng going
on then i ought to
know
about
it
otherwise it seems
like
youre
disappearing of
f hours at a time
and l
eaving me in my
sundto
entertain
ourself i do
apologize
ed
mr
s
wa i just need a
little
time and then
things we
back to
know i would think
you
can be patient for
anot
her
hour so on your
own cant
you i dont
appreciate
the
flippancy young
man tell me whats
goin
g
on
everyone three
dead bod
ies have appeared
aroun
d the
house and we
suspect th
at 太诡异
了他们对于死神的态
度 but were
dealing wit
h it everythings
under
control
well i dont see
why yo
u let that
stranger in
here in the first
place
is your own fault
as f
ar as iccan
cy 感觉每一个正常人 stay
at
dy please dont
try and
tell me what to
do like i
said im sorting
it
out certainly
doesnt l
ook like youre
doing m
uch of
anything did you
find
ring or did you
just gi
ve
up 对他完全就没管
了还在考虑自己的那些事
情 you can have it
back if you
like 我不想要
了 i gave you this
ring
for a reason eddy
啊 where is my
daughter your
dot i should hope
you h
avent forgotten
about
her in all this
commotion i think
i mad
e it very clear
earlier what i
expected
of
you if somethings
to h
er
emond then theyll
be
consequences i am
like
the
greing like you
asked if you
expected m
e to do anything
else then you
should ha
ve told me
啊是这样的逻辑 with
me
young very
she
well i havent
seen any
one else
arrive and ive
kept tr
ack of everyone
whos c
ome through the
door 本来 i thought
you w
as asleep in your
room you re to go
ther
e now and
reconcile wit
h her and take the
ring and
this im so
sorry it
it she
啊 your
daughter
dad 他们这种反应好怪
啊你为什么不早复
说 i want you your
dauli
er II diknow you
you do
nt the my my
safety
IIII my my IIHH ut
TAA
uua a
host you dont
know how
your daughter is i
you you think have
a
doughter excuse
me
you you TT your
dauuter i dont
you your you
ua
you you dont
expect me
to look out for
everyo
ne just because
the man
of the
out i dont dont
even
have a daughter to
do
you
you you think
me 好岁人
吗 i
will and my son
has 这
个 i dont know why
i tr
usted you all
along ive been
trying
to be polite and
curtious and for
what y
oure as much a
strange
r to me as anyone
啊
滚 now everyone
else wil
l be rushing into
save
you that suits me
just
fine 被老被害熟
了
好千万别 moch 有这种啊啊是有点
奇
怪嗯
嗯谢谢吴维
维谢谢吴维维
的谢谢晚
安米米星日入
梦这游戏里的
人哎
呀这游戏里人的脑回路真的很神
秘狂死人就是没什么想到报
警有
报想到报
警但是想隐
瞒但是真的是这里面死了人之
后他们就会忘掉这个人是谁
吗那个玛莎不说是不认
识但他实际上认不认识令二话
啊那个之前那个管家死了之
后这艾迪也说不认识
的然后那个他女儿死了之
后他也说不认识鲍
告不知道爆成功了没
有因为连后面两个死人的发现人都是艾迪
吧
是但是海伦是还记得女儿的艾迪是不是真
的
的说明天早上
哦好
吧有没有忘掉
了记得衣服洗
了不
是他是经过反复的提醒之
哦
对女儿
哦你有女儿
哦你女儿好像死
了这种就是一种遗
忘但是遗忘都不彻底的那种感
觉然后又说觉得不认识
他主要是一直在说不认识
他先说的是
哦原来你有个女儿
啊那女儿
好你女儿好像死
了因为死了个女
的但是我不认识那个人是
谁大概是这种感
觉
嗯现在看起来是这样的对
啊您说说
吧你根本你看这里又那个你在乎你女儿怎
么怎么
样接着就是你说什
么你根本没有女儿
吧难道你也跟这事有关
系感觉嗯很怪
的然后这很
怪这里又说你和其他陌生人没两
样然后艾迪走
了剩下海龙和另外几个人赶过
来有白金
吗
哦我就利亚喝大米
啊而且这个梦还是一直在进行
的
嗯什么意
思居然不
是那 a
饼应该是走了的
呀 ID 走
了那就是其他人也听到
喽安妮他们也听到了谢鬼 GP 的粉色
灯
牌
嗯对还说
了其他所有人说所有人都会听
到但是这两个已经死
了肯定不算
吗那难道还有人不在
哦十二楼是
吧人数
es whos
eve
eve whos
eve whos he 好
吗肯德基 whats going
on 哈
好 i dont know
啊挡个
雷他又死了
吗
哦对
啊 another
one we heard
someone in
here a moment to
go did anyone see
what
he
went ID 好想你
玩 what
happening why is
everyo
ne in
here 好憨
呐 im glad you all
right so its
true theyre
coming
back get that man
away
from
me i have
done nothing 没
有 whatever evil
has com
e into your
house 还真是按顺序
啊有人知道他是谁
吗也许 is she
dad 托
尼那是你妈
呀 its the same as
all
the others someone
is t
rying to scare
us 对
对 im sure they
must ha
ve been dead for a
while i dont
think
so the body still
warn but surely
someone
would have noticed
if
four people would
walki
ng around the
house 哈
哈 i dont
understand wh
ere they came
from this is the
force it could be
some
sort of
disease maybe they
will
escape from some
hospi
tal
nearby tell
me please take
this
serious isnt
anyone go
ing to 看来不是那个人的 v
is in
the
room
yeah
thanks at least
joonen i were
invited but
somehow
listen were all
going
to go to bed and
lock o
ur
doors 他们连自己妈妈都不识
了但是但是 helen 刚刚认识
了还记得衣
服
哎麻
烦哎
呀
yes 这里才说名少才到
啊 they wont be
able to
get here until the
morning
good 这才说明天彩到 lock
your
doors and dont
let any
strangers
in can we all
agree on
that im not going
to a
nything
fine everyone else
go s
traight to your
rooms w
ill talk
again tomorrow
morning i 是
的海伦之前和那个卫生间的水电主器只有
一个孩
子但是最后走过来的时候又想起来
了 good night and
sleep
well 还是说临死之前会想得起来这
种下一个谁
记起
来下一个谁记起
来海伦是谁就轮到他
了那下一个是
谁那达米安马上就记得起来海伦是谁了
吗
啊自己恢复的时候就是死什我不知道啊衣
服是是
谁您受伤了
吗还是说整一个故事都是一个什么隐
喻就是看表面上看起来是
人实际上不是人这首别
吧看看其他人直接回房
间我我早上早上再谈纸
条没有纸
条对
啊你要想一开始你们还记得第一个死的
人就只有管家认得是谁
吗如果管家没多久就死
了打下一个雷的时候就死
了然后那个管家死了之
后其他人下来都不认识这个管
家对
吧然后嗯这怎么就怎么说
嗯不认识那个管家
柔他调的那个热可可上去给那个衣服喝了
柔衣
服提到了管
家他说这个和管家调的一
样这衣服这记忆没有出问
题然后那个呃好
的
哎艾迪还说
哎你认识你认识
哎那个桑三顿
吗他还问了问完了之后没多
久然后弄衣服就死
了然后衣服这里的事情之
后下一个不是海伦
吗刘海伦也是说你对衣服做了什
么也是他好像是唯一一
个还记得衣服的
人目前三个都有有这个特征
呢对他对于古人家的记忆点是肉扣
扣就是下一个记能够记得死者的人紧接着
都死
了但是现在目前大家都说不认识海
伦海伦在客厅的时候还不记得衣
服是
的我进了台球
室忽然就想起来
了然后他没多久就死
了那是不是意味着卢伯特前面有人也有死
人不知道
哦抽我一会
啊但是现在现在我们该干嘛来
着难道没人打算指出房间里面已经有两个
陌生人了
吗是因为那个海伦和衣
服
嗯是因为海伦和伊芙都死
了然后其实就他们出现在这个房这个房子
里
面是因为衣服是他的未婚
妻然后伊服和海伦都死
了
话就只剩下托尼一个人
了然后安妮在安妮的眼
中托尼托尼跟救恩都是和其他人毫无关系
的两个陌生
人
了是这样的
吗
嗯
对托尼已经没有出现在这里的理由
了是
吗
嗨还有英国
的
嗯然后但是现在已经一点
了到时候的说对邀请的试
试然后刚刚好十三是过夜点是
吗十三是过夜点的
话十三大家都在自己的房间里
面托尼的房间是托尼
啊不是
吗要怎么过
啊托尼的房间已经不属于托尼
了海里海伦的房间是谁的
呀
哦对
哦约翰没拉过
来有原
因但是鲁伯特死
了所以约翰过来就变成奇怪的是是
了那托尼的房间不止托尼
了
哎我们我们当是已经知道下一
个大概谁会死
了就是有人关上柜
吗
嗯回到家中好
呃睡前还查了一下资
料然后维多利亚的房间的话应该有画
泡达米安两个
人
对可能达米安在死前又想到
了是不是主要这真
的他们对于死人没有什么感
觉是不是在睡觉之
前他要突然说一
下想起来谁了之类
的 II just want to
check i dont want
one
jumping out of the
ward
robe in the middle
of o
f the
night come on
big no ones
hiding anybodies
in her
e
啊 i know sweet 的什么
好
处 and ive got you
to p
rotect me from any
stra
ngers 电
台 of
course
不 please dont run
up l
ike that
again 找个陌生人找个这个可以没
跳
ch im always here
for
you we you leave
first
哦天
呐它实体还是温热
的然且开始翻找东西那
种 mister hobes is
a sus
picious character
isonty were an
agreeme
nt about that 房间的角
色他们肯定是到哪个地方 to
believe
him but he seems
the so
rt of man who
would str
uggle to tell
AI but i know what
you
mean what was he
doing
that the listening
to a
conversation 不是直接进
来 its vot
ters those people
are w
atching me
with 我们在
come are this
place muc
h
longer ill go
mad i know the
whole bu
siness with the
bodies
is
upsetting but i
dont t
hink think meant
for us
everyand if
any comfort t
everyone
else talked to
says the
y like you so
come dont think
think
think dont trust
out and why did
you pla
y the piano
earlier any
anything
happen why i 跟好好聊
天 just wanted to
see yo
u sweet
out come
on come to
bed i dont like
this h
ouse
vik i dont feel
savier well be
alright
if youre really
worried we can
just kee
p the door locked
until
the police
arrive maybe we
should
good and then we
ll go
to hit mom first
thing
in the morning
winter
cut thats the
name of
your moms
house 没有红色的拼
乓
对 and i promise
you lik
e it a lot more
than th
is
place
嗯给怀表上发
条
对
sweetoed what that
he r
emember it
mrs douwill asked
me to
find it over
dinner
哦完了
哦他知道这是谁
了然后他又死
了 i dont realize
it what what are
you ta
lking
about 大夫人是
谁这种 anyone
anything how
watch with
missing she asked
me
good
哎真的是这个意
思 until son was
there
too 他时常对他想起来
了 you
mean the body
earlier did you
know
her of
course i did vick
and t
he other should
have re
cognized her
two they must have
know
n all the dead
bodies t
hat hiding
something ca
lm
down sweet
coat
please no
something
wrong 看来就是我们推测的那个方
向
啊
wrong he wouldnt
lie t
o
me would
you of
course i wouldnt
then
who were you
talking
to just before i
found
you in the living
room you said you
were
talk wasnt
swethered but i
dont k
now whats good
应应该就是我们刚刚说的良
心 im sorry
买 i hope you want
else
in this house is
lying
through their
teeth we cant
trust an
y of
it doesnt
matter 反正 no one
can hu
rt us in
here lets go to
sleep and you can
expla
in it to all to me
in t
he
morning all
right i love you
ick but i cant
wait to
get out of
here i love you
too sweet
out everything
will be
just
find 居然没有他醒不过来的剧情
吗 ok 这下他该死
了哼哎呦嗯 gonna sake
哦我们但是我们不只是第二次了
呀难道第一次不算恢复电力
哦给了我们一个那个证据研究笔记十五
v 的 W
D 谁的房
间一二四五七
哦一二三四零四日期都是前面的维多利利
亚的房间
哦
对那十五的时候是这个算是提示
了但我们十三还没有看完
呢马上呢刚想是自己的温柔被花掉
的应该也是一些补全信息
的
嗯不起着看之后的
吗车
盘不过这边应该都不会再有什么剧
情他们自言自语应该没有什么线索就是
了 look at this
mess
嗯 i dont
know i dont keep
out t
hese
things ive been a
lot
happy if i got
riad of
it all and started
again 哼
哎难道玛莎他那个汽
指他说他不知道是自己那个为什么要戴着
戒
指可能因为什么什么这个玛莎是不是本身
是那个鲁伯
特佳丽的妻子
啊然后又因为他来的时
候那个卢伯特家里不是已经死了
吗所以他想不起
来但是那个
谁但是那个管家还记
得
对应该是因为他说他的名字是他自己改
的没有讲他为什么改这个名
字刚烤炉子是第一次
的
嗯应该是看样
子然后还有了的房间可能没有
了达米安死了之
后维多利亚马上要想起达米安
了笑死你去书房
吗奥数自己是最后一个嘉
宾也可以是罗伯特纽带关系段罗队的嗯
is is
the is ggone 行
啊校准天降这边只是普普通通的在睡
觉好
啊不聊这些
了哈哈哈
哈大米安不见
喽胳膊吃
了睡救
了然后说嗯阁楼他叫一声吓了一
跳正常窗户开着外面在下
雨这么大的鱼开窗睡觉
哦总感觉会地板会遭罪
啊个 p 萨 ty winter
OK
哦原来你有打算关
上是
的但其实这些房间里面米天好像去米天好
像也更喜欢
阁楼一点
啊就相对来说另外几个房间
哎也有不喜欢就是嗯三 tony 不知
道玛
莎然后迪艾迪会回自己房间
吗哦
哦那埃 g 难道是和托尼一
起那应该是艾迪去
了托尼的房
间易燃
全看样子是请聆听他视
听还记得机器
人那把枪骂骂姐姐都没
了但是没印
象哇啊哎 d know 某人在
打哈哈
哈我在锁衣柜里面锁衣柜还真有
用他拿枪去
了路人在他啊广有人还在打鼾
米汀以为自己游戏卡
了
嗯
好这下
哦海伦伊芙和桑顿这三个人都死
了那这样的话我们已经确认完
了刚刚好玩的
嗯玩完了一
半今天就先停在这里
了十
三结束了十四应该感觉还是从维多利亚和
达米按这里
开
始但是可能就没有打眠
了你听猜一个维多利亚这边就只需要每维
多利亚一个
人了怎么
样
嗯啊果然啊啊对
了 what 我我可知道
了好哈好吧哈嗯
OK 然后应该直接就是那个
了
好就停在这里
吧看来我们的猜测是没错
的应该之后也还是会比较顺
利嗯
嗯是
的这下真的是有个雷霆大尸体
了但是虽然推出了这一层还是不理解为什
么会这样
啊是因为这个呃装置本身就是回忆
嘛没办法补
全不知道的事情就不知
道每天也没办法补
全自己不理解的事
情也不一定是弹钢琴
了刚才那个也说不上是在
弹可能是在砸毒
药还是怎么就肯定不是毒药了
吧打雷作为死人的那
个我这屋子有什么诅
咒主要是我们其实看到
的本来又不是真实的故
事所以解释方式有很多
种但是我下回下回我们目前还没有安排
哦明天早上是早
歌然后明天晚上是有联
动明天晚上有联
动应该是明天白天会发那个联动的通
车说句写岁什么
的
嗯然后星期期四休
息星期五的
话星期五早台式的司
机那起码要都星期六星期天
了谢 TD 电
影想吃棒棒
糖豆腐三灯
牌
哎谢谢嘘不
得中午多早起码要周六回首周日
了电电玩是通关
吗嗯
嗯今晚是肯定可以通
关
对但我们还有实质存在腰盘
呢他手机要看
吗总之谢谢大
家今天来看我们这个叫什么来
着佳丽宅体悬案的第一
回大概应该是两回左右能完结
啊谢谢大家参
与下一次可能就要想一想名字
了没
事印象米汀感觉印象还算挺深刻
的流程还有百分之五十五左
右后面的应该还是能推的比较顺的
吧感觉现在死人速度加快
了不是
吗
哦谢谢谢谢冰布多
芬谢谢冰布洛芬的提
督谢谢你续费的提督并不能分好人大
气长生乐
老健健康
康永远不
死谢谢你的提
督感谢谢谢谢谢上谢谢你的提
督谢谢谢
谢那那么我们下次再
见剧情缺少一
点毕竟是有原作
的
嗯可能会有别的展
开到时候但米金觉得目前为止我们还是挺
顺利
的没有出现那种比较长时间的卡
关不知道怎么推进这种情
况
嗯人物关系也没有像鲁特里一家那么复
杂那么宽庞大的一个网看马当说谢谢大
家今天晚上来自米汀看这个悬案
啊我拜
拜拜
拜拜拜嗨爸
爸
嘿写作已
景写作已景的小花
花写
US 写 ES
读我是
CC 晚安你好
梦明天早哥再
见还好一个人睡觉不
会第二天旁边出现陌生
人好
的晚安太
太你一个人睡
觉
嗯
对想了一
想目前的游戏剧情虽然还不知道另外几个
人起来的时
候的反
应但至少不会凭空出现
了晚
安那不好
说对他们来
说他们一直都是一个人睡的雪梨雪灵音的
音
面因为我怕不敢睡觉
了快好水
啊可是小樱花触碰本
西晚安记得
哦锅蝶三角
过可能你是晚
安有可能一出
头希望明天钱嗓子也能比较清醒
了什么意
思写不清
楚太何
了晚安谢虚空喵的水晶
鞋谁暴罗的留下的
爱谢谢虚无喵的十五三幺九棉花
糖谢谢谢鸦片狗狗王的一
面晚安晚安希望我不
要因为突然想起谁之后突然死
我他不
会但是米
青其实现在很想去看一下游戏评
论但是感觉看游戏评论百分之百会被剧
透我不太能去
看还是等着
吧慢慢等
吧谢旭哥
喵谢旭哥喵的十五删到十六爱心抱
枕请你的爱心抱
枕谢
谢不看不
看谢谢
了冰布勒
芬谢拼布洛芬的喜欢
你谢谢你喜欢
你谢谢灵异的友谊的小
船谢谢大
家快来
嗯
对完全没玩过的
话就算看到巨头楼也没办法跟剧情联边
上所以会忘
掉但是你要是玩到一半的
话再去看剧
透就没办法再还原一个没没看过的脑子嗯